<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SportsNewsHistoryRecords</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="serie_a_history1">
        Serie A, also called Serie A TIM due to sponsorship by TIM, is a professional league competition for football clubs located at the top of the Italian football league system and has been operating for over eighty years since the 1929–30 season. It had been organized by Lega Calcio until 2010, but a new league, the Lega Serie A, was created for the 2010–11 season. Serie A is regarded as one of the best football leagues in the world and it is often depicted as the most tactical national league. Serie A is the world\'s second-strongest national league according to IFFHS and has produced the highest number of European Cup finalists: Italian clubs have reached the final of the competition on a record 26 different occasions, winning the title 12 times. Serie A is ranked fourth among European leagues according to UEFA\'s league coefficient, behind La Liga, Bundesliga and Premier League, which is based on the performance of Italian clubs in the Champions League and the Europa League during the last five years. Serie A led the UEFA ranking from 1986 to 1988 and from 1990 to 1999.\n
    </string>

     <string name="serie_a_history2">
         In its current format, the Italian Football Championship was revised from having regional and interregional rounds, to a single-tier league from the 1929–30 season onwards. The championship titles won prior to 1929 are officially recognised by FIGC with the same weighting as titles that were subsequently awarded. However, the 1945–46 season, when the league was played over two geographical groups due to the ravages of WWII, is not statistically considered, even if its title is fully official. All the winning teams are recognised with the title of Champion of Italy, which is ratified by the Lega Serie A before the start of the next edition of the championship.\n
    </string>

     <string name="serie_a_history3">
The league hosts three of the world\'s most famous clubs as Juventus, Milan and Internazionale, all founding members of the G-14, a group which represented the largest and most prestigious European football clubs; Serie A was the only league to produce three founding members. More players have won the coveted Ballon d\'Or award while playing at a Serie A club than any other league in the world. - ahead of Spain\'s La Liga, although the actual number of Ballon d\'Or won by players in these two leagues is equal at 18 each if including the FIFA Ballon d\'Or. Milan is the second club with the most official international titles in the world, with 18. Juventus, Italy\'s most successful club of the 20th century and the most successful Italian team, is tied for fourth in Europe and eighth in the world in the same ranking. The club is the only one in the world to have won all possible official continental competitions and the world title. Internazionale, following their achievements in the 2009–10 season, became the first Italian team to have achieved a treble. Juventus, Milan and Inter, along with Roma, Fiorentina, Lazio and Napoli, are known as the Seven Sisters of Italian football.\n
     </string>
    <string name="serie_a_history4">
For most of Serie A\'s history, there were 16 or 18 clubs competing at the top level. Since 2004–05, however, there have been 20 clubs altogether. One season (1947–48) was played with 21 teams for political reasons. Below is a complete record of how many teams played in each season throughout the league\'s history;\n
•	18 clubs: 1929–1934\n
•	16 clubs: 1934–1942\n
•	18 clubs: 1942–1946\n
•	20 clubs: 1946–1947\n
•	21 clubs: 1947–1948\n
•	20 clubs: 1948–1952\n
•	18 clubs: 1952–1967\n
•	16 clubs: 1967–1988\n
•	18 clubs: 1988–2004\n
•	20 clubs: 2004–present
    </string>

    <string name="team_recors_title">
                Team records\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_recors_team">
Most championships won\n
Overall\n
•	32, Juventus\n
        \n
Consecutives\n
•	5, Juventus (1930–31 season to 1934–35 season and from 2011–12 season to 2015–16 season)\n
•	5, Torino (1942–43 season and the 1945–46 season to 1948–49 season)\n
•	5, Internazionale (2005–06 season to 2009–10 season)\n
        \n
Most seasons in Serie A\n
•	84, Internazionale\n
         \n
Most seasons in Serie B\n
•	57, Brescia\n
        \n
Most points in a season\n
2 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1928–29\n
•	4, Bologna\n
6 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1926–27\n
•	14, Torino\n
8 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1927–28 - 1945–46\n
•	22, Torino 1945–46\n
16 Teams (2 points per win) 1934–35 to 1942–43 - 1967–68 to 1987–88\n
•	51, Juventus 1976–77\n
18 Teams (2 points per win) 1929–30 to 1933–34 - 1952–53 to 1966–67 - 1988–89 to 1993–94\n
•	58, Internazionale 1988–89\n
18 Teams (3 points per win) 1994–95 to 2003–04\n
•	82, Milan 2003–04\n
20 Teams (2 points per win) 1946–47 - 1948–49 to 1951–52\n
•	63, Torino 1946–47\n
20 Teams (3 points per win) 2004–05 to present\n
•	102, Juventus 2013–14\n
21 Teams (2 points per win) 1947–48\n
•	65, Torino\n
         \n
Most consecutive wins\n
•	17, Internazionale, 2006–07\n
•	15, Juventus, 2015–16\n
•	13, Juventus, 2013–14 to 2014–15\n
•	12, Juventus, 2013–14\n
•	11, Roma, 2005–06 and 2012–13 to 2013–14\n
•	10, Juventus, 2015-16\n
•	10, Juventus, 1931–32\n
•	10, Milan, 1950–51 and 1989–90\n
•	10, Bologna, 1963–64\n
        \n
Most consecutive home wins\n
•	25, Juventus, 2013–14 to 2014–15\n
        \n
Longest win streaks from the start of a Serie A season\n
•	10, Roma, 2013–14\n
        \n
Longest win streaks without conceding from the start of a Serie A season\n
•	5, Juventus, 2014–15\n
        \n
Most wins in season\n
•	33, Juventus, 2013–14 (38 matches)\n
•	30, Internazionale, 2006–07 (38 matches)\n
•	29, Torino, 1947–48 (40 matches)\n
•	28, Juventus, 2015–16 (38 matches)\n
•	28, Milan, 2005–06 (38 matches)\n
•	27, Internazionale, 1950–51 (38 matches)\n
        \n
Most home wins in season\n
•	19, Juventus, 2013–14 (19 matches)\n
        \n
Most matches won\n
•	1495, Juventus\n
        \n
Most goals scored\n
•	4577, Juventus\n
        \n
Longest unbeaten streaks\n
•	58, Milan, 1990–91 to 1992–93 (26 May 1991, 0–0 v Parma; 21 March 1993, 0–1 v Parma)\n
•	49, Juventus, 2010–11 to 2012–13 (22 May 2011, 2–2 v Napoli; 3 November 2012, 1–3 v Internazionale)\n
        \n
Longest unbeaten streaks in a single Serie A season\n
16 Teams\n
•	30, Perugia, 1978–79\n
18 Teams\n
•	34, Milan, 1991–92\n
20 Teams\n
•	38, Juventus, 2011–12
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="individual_records_title">
                Individual records\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_individual_records">
Most championships won\n
8 Championships\n
•	Virginio Rosetta (2 with Pro Vercelli + 6 with Juventus)\n
•	Giovanni Ferrari (5 with Juventus + 2 with Inter + 1 with Bologna)\n
•	Giuseppe Furino (all with Juventus)\n
        \n
7 Championships\n
•	Roberto Bettega (all with Juventus)\n
•	Alessandro Costacurta (all with Milan)\n
•	Ciro Ferrara (2 with Napoli + 5 with Juventus)\n
•	Paolo Maldini (all with Milan)\n
•	Gaetano Scirea (all with Juventus)\n
•	Guglielmo Gabetto (2 with Juventus + 5 with Torino)\n
•	Gianluigi Buffon (all with Juventus)\n

    </string>

    <string name="top_scorers_title">
        Top Scorers\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_scorers">
1.	Italy	Silvio Piola,	years: 1929–1954 274 goals\n
2.	Italy	Francesco Totti,	years: 1992–present 248 goals\n
3.	Sweden	Gunnar Nordahl,	years: 1948–1958	225 goals\n
4.	Italy	Giuseppe Meazza,	years: 1929–1947	216 goals\n
5.  Italy	José Altafini,	years: 1958–1976	216 goals\n
6.	Italy	Antonio Di Natale,	years: 2002–present	208 goals\n
7.	Italy	Roberto Baggio,	years: 1985–2004	205 goals\n
8.	Sweden	Kurt Hamrin,	    years: 1956–1971	190 goals\n
9.	Italy	Giuseppe Signori, years: 1991–2004	188 goals\n
10. Italy	Alessandro Del Piero,	years: 1993–2012	188 goals
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_history">
        The Primera Division (First Division) of the Liga de Futbol Profesional (LFP), commonly known in English as La Liga, is the top professional association football division of the Spanish football league system. It is officially named Liga BBVA (BBVA League) for sponsorship reasons. It is contested by 20 teams, with the three lowest-placed teams relegated to the Segunda Division and replaced by the top two teams in that division plus the winner of a playoff.\n
A total of 60 teams have competed in La Liga since its inception. Nine teams have been crowned champions, with Real Madrid winning the title a record 32 times and Barcelona 23 times. Real Madrid dominated the championship from the 1950s through the 1980s. Since the 1990s, however, Real Madrid and Barcelona have both dominated, although La Liga has seen other champions, including Atletico Madrid, Valencia, and Deportivo de La Coruna. In more recent years, Atletico Madrid has joined a coalition of now three teams dominating La Liga alongside Real Madrid and Barcelona.\n
La Liga has been the top league in Europe over the last five years, according to UEFA league coefficient and La Liga clubs have been the top rated club in Europe more times than any other league (18) double that of second placed Serie A with (9). La Liga based clubs have also won the most IFFS World\'s Club Team of the Year awards (9). La Liga clubs have won the most UEFA Champions League tournaments (15) and Real Madrid are the competition\'s most successful club, with ten titles.\n
        La Liga clubs have also won the highest number of UEFA Cup,UEFA Europa League titles and Sevilla are the most successful club in the competition\'s history with 4 titles. La Liga is the first and only league to be represented by both finalists in a UEFA Champions League final on two occasions.\n
        La Liga-based players have won the highest number of FIFA World Player of the Year awards (11), Ballon d\'Or awards (19) and UEFA Best Player in Europe awards (4).\n
        La Liga players also represent the most FIFPro World XI and UEFA Team of the Year places. Real Madrid and Barcelona are the La Liga clubs to have won the UEFA Champions League.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_foundation_title">
        Foundation\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_foundation">
In April 1927, José María Acha, a director at Arenas Club de Getxo, first proposed the idea of a national league in Spain. After much debate about the size of the league and who would take part, the Real Federación Española de Fútbol eventually agreed on the ten teams who would form the first Primera División in 1929. Barcelona, Real Madrid, Athletic Bilbao, Real Sociedad, Arenas Club de Getxo and Real Unión were all selected as previous winners of the Copa del Rey. Atlético Madrid, Espanyol and Europa qualified as Copa del Rey runners-up and Racing de Santander qualified through a knockout competition. Only three of the founding clubs, Real Madrid, Barcelona and Athletic Bilbao, have never been relegated from the Primera División.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title1">
        The 1930s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_30">
        Although Barcelona won the very first Liga in 1929 and Real Madrid won their first titles in 1932 and 1933, it was Athletic Bilbao that set the early pace winning Primera División in 1930, 1931, 1934 and 1936. They were also runners-up in 1932 and 1933. In 1935, Real Betis, then known as Betis Balompié, won their only title to date. Primera División was suspended during the Spanish Civil War.\n
In 1937, the teams in the Republican area of Spain, with the notable exception of the two Madrid clubs, competed in the Mediterranean League and Barcelona emerged as champions. Seventy years later, on 28 September 2007, Barcelona requested the RFEF to recognise that title as a Liga title. This action was taken after RFEF was asked to recognise Levante FC\'s Copa de la España Libre win as equivalent to Copa del Rey trophy. Nevertheless, the governing body of Spanish football has not made an outright decision yet.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title2">
        The 1940s\n
        </string>

    <string name="la_liga_40">
        When the Primera División resumed after the Spanish Civil War, it was Atlético Aviación (nowadays Atlético Madrid), Valencia, and Sevilla that initially emerged as the strongest clubs. Atlético were only awarded a place during the 1939–40 season as a replacement for Real Oviedo, whose ground had been damaged during the war. The club subsequently won their first Liga title and retained it in 1941. While other clubs lost players to exile, execution, and as casualties of the war, the Atlético team was reinforced by a merger. The young, pre-war squad of Valencia had also remained intact and in the post-war years matured into champions, gaining three Liga titles in1942, 1944, and 1947. They were also runners-up in 1948 and 1949. Sevilla also enjoyed a brief golden era, finishing as runners-up in 1940 and 1942 before winning their only title to date in 1946. By the latter part of the decade, Barcelona began to emerge as a force when they were crowned champions in 1945, 1948 and 1949\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title3">
    Di Stéfano, Puskás, Kubala and Suárez\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_50">
        Naturalised Argentine Alfredo Di Stéfano was part of a dominant Real Madrid side in the 1950s\n
Although Atlético Madrid, previously known as Atlético Aviación, were champions in 1950 and 1951 under catenaccio mastermind Helenio Herrera, the 1950s saw the beginning of the Barcelona/Real Madrid dominance. During the 1930s, 1940s, and 1950s, there were strict limits imposed on foreign players. In most cases, clubs could only have three foreign players in their squads, meaning that at least eight local players had to play in every game. During the 1950s, however, these rules were circumvented by Real Madrid and Barcelona, who naturalized Alfredo Di Stéfano, Ferenc Puskás, and Ladislav Kubala. Inspired by Kubala, Barça won the title in 1952 and 1953. Di Stéfano, Puskás, and Francisco Gento formed the nucleus of the Real Madrid team that dominated the second half of the 1950s. Madrid won the first division for the first time as Real Madrid in 1954 and retained its title in 1955. They were winners again in 1957 and 1958, with only Athletic Bilbao interrupting their sequence. During this period, Real Madrid also won an unprecedented five consecutive European Cups. Barcelona, with a team coached by Helenio Herrera and featuring Luis Suárez, won the title in 1959 and 1960.\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_title4">
    The Madrid years\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_60">
Between 1961 and 1980, Real Madrid dominated the Primera División, being crowned champion 14 times. This included a five-in-a-row sequence from 1961 to 1965 and two three-in-a-row sequences (1967–1969 and 1978–1980). During this era, only Atlético Madrid offered Real Madrid any serious challenge, adding four more titles to their tally in 1966, 1970, 1973, and 1977. Of the other clubs, only Valencia in 1971 and the Johan Cruyff-inspired Barcelona of 1974 managed to break the dominance of Real Madrid.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title5">
        The Madrid winning sequence was ended more significantly in 1981 when Real Sociedad won their first-ever title. They retained it in 1982 and their two in a row was followed by another by their fellow Basques Athletic Bilbao, who won back-to-back titles in 1983 and 1984. Terry Venables led Barcelona to a solitary title in 1985 before Real Madrid won again another five in a row sequence (1986–1990) with a team guided by Leo Beenhakker and including Hugo Sánchez and the legendary La Quinta del Buitre – Emilio Butragueño, Manolo Sanchís, Martín Vázquez, Míchel and Miguel Pardeza.\n
    </string>

 <string name="la_liga_title6">
    The 1990s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_90">
        Johan Cruyff returned to Barcelona as manager in 1988, and assembled the legendary Dream Team. Cruyff introduced players like Pep Guardiola, Jose Mari Bakero,Txiki Begiristain, Andoni Goikoetxea, Ronald Koeman, Michael Laudrup, Romario and Hristo Stoichkov. This team won Primera Division four times between 1991 and 1994 and won the European Cup in 1992. Laudrup then moved to arch rivals Real Madrid, and helped them end Barcelona\'s run in 1995. Atletico Madrid won their ninth Primera Division title in 1996 before Real Madrid added another Liga trophy to their cabinet in 1997. After the success of Cruyff, another Dutchman – Ajax manager Louis van Gaal – arrived at the Camp Nou, and with the talents of Luis Figo, Luis Enrique, and Rivaldo, Barcelona again won the title in 1998 and 1999.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title7">
    The 2000s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_00">
As Primera División entered a new century, the Big Two of Real Madrid and Barcelona found themselves facing new challengers. Between 1993 and 2004, Deportivo La Coruña finished in the top three on ten occasions, a better record than either Real Madrid or Barcelona, and in 2000, under Javier Irureta, they became the ninth team to be crowned champions. Real Madrid won two more Liga titles in 2001 and 2003 and also the UEFA Champions League in 2000 and 2002, and won their 30th league title in 2007 after a three-year drought. They were challenged by a re-emerging Valencia in both competitions. Under the management of Héctor Cúper, Valencia finished as Champions League runners-up in 2000 and 2001. His successor, Rafael Benítez, built on this and led the club to a Liga title in 2002 and winning the double with a league title and the UEFA Cup in 2004. The 2004–05 season saw a resurgent Barcelona, inspired by the brilliant Ronaldinho, win their first title of the new century, in addition to the Liga-Champions League double in 2005–06. With world-class players like Raúl, Ruud van Nistelrooy and Gonzalo Higuaín, Real Madrid won back-to-back La Liga titles in 2006–07 and 2007–08 season. Under Pep Guardiola\'s Dream Team, powered by La Masia talents such as Lionel Messi, Xavi and Andrés Iniesta, Barcelona added three straight Liga titles (2008–09, 2009–10 and 2010–11).\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_title8">
    The 2010s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_10">
In the 2011–12 season, Real Madrid won its 32nd title under the management of José Mourinho with a record-breaking points tally of 100, a record 121 number of goals scored, most overall (32) and away (16) wins in a single season in La Liga history. Barcelona coach Tito Vilanova matched the 100-point record a year later in 2012–13 while battling terminal cancer. Atlético Madrid won the 2013–14 title, their first in 18 years, and the first title in ten years that Real Madrid or Barcelona had not won. Barcelona won the 2014–15 season.\n
</string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_title">
        TEAM RECORDS\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team1">
        Titles\n
•	Most League Titles: 32, Real Madrid (1931–32, 1932–33, 1953–54, 1954–55, 1956–57, 1957–58, 1960–61, 1961–62, 1962–63, 1963–64, 1964–65, 1966–67, 1967–68, 1968–69, 1971–72, 1974–75, 1975–76, 1977–78, 1978–79, 1979–80, 1985–86, 1986–87, 1987–88, 1988–89, 1989–90, 1994–95, 1996–97, 2000–01, 2002–03,2006–07, 2007–08, 2011–12)\n
•	Most Consecutive League Titles: 5, Real Madrid (twice): (1960–61, 1961–62, 1962–63, 1963–64, 1964–65),(1985–86, 1986–87, 1987–88, 1988–89, 1989–90)\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_records_team2">
Top flight appearances\n
•	Most Appearances: 86, joint record (till 2015–16)\n
•	Athletic Bilbao (1929–present)\n
•	F. C. Barcelona (1929–present)\n
•	Real Madrid (1929–present)\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team3">
        Wins\n
•	Most wins overall: 1590, Real Madrid\n
•	Most wins in a season: 32, Real Madrid (2011–12), Barcelona (2012–13)\n
•	Most home wins in a season: 18, joint record:\n
•	Real Madrid (1987–88and (2009–10)\n
•	Barcelona (2009–10) and (2012–13)\n
•	Most away wins in a season: 16, Real Madrid (2011–12)\n
•	Most consecutive wins: 16, Barcelona (2010–11)\n
•	Most consecutive home wins: 39, Barcelona (16 February 1958 to 6 November 1960\n
•	Most consecutive away wins: 12, Barcelona (1 May 2010 to 12 February 2011)\n

•	100% home win record in a season:\n
•	Athletic Bilbao (9 games; 1933–34)\n
•	Athletic Bilbao (11 games; 1935–36)\n
•	Barcelona (13 games; 1948–49)\n
•	Barcelona (15 games; 1952–53)\n
•	Sevilla (15 games; 1956–57)\n
•	Barcelona (15 games; 1958–59)\n
•	Barcelona (15 games; 1959–60)\n
•	Real Madrid (15 games; 1959–60)\n
•	Real Madrid (15 games; 1962–63)\n
•	Real Madrid (17 games; 1985–86)\n
•	Longest win streaks from the start of a season: 9, Real Madrid ( 1968–69)\n

    </string>

      <string name="la_liga_records_team4">
        Draws\n
•	Most draws overall: 609, Athletic Bilbao\n
•	Most draws in a season: 17, joint record:\n
•	Espanyol (1997–98)\n
•	Racing Santander (1996–97)\n
•	Rayo Vallecano (1992–93)\n
•	Burgos (1990–91)\n
•	Mallorca (1989–90)\n
•	CD Málaga (1971–72)\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team5">
Losses\n
•	Most losses overall: 1024, Espanyol\n
•	Most losses in a season: 29, Sporting Gijón (1997–98)\n
•	Most consecutive losses in a season: 11, Las Palmas (13 December 1959 to 28 February 1960)\n
   </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team6">
    Points\n
    •	Most points overall in the top flight: 4110, Real Madrid\n
    •	Most points in a season overall: 100 (87.72% of points), Real Madrid (2011–12) and Barcelona (2012–13)\n
    •	Most points in a season home: 55, Barcelona\n
    •	Most points in a season away: 50, Real Madrid (2011–12)\n
    •	Most points in a season opening half: 55, Barcelona (2012–13)\n
    •	Most points in a season closing half: 52, Real Madrid (2009–10)\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team7">
Games without a loss\n
•	Most consecutive league games without a loss: 38, Real Sociedad, (29 April 1979 to 11 May 1980)\n
•	Most consecutive league games without a loss home: 121, Real Madrid (17 February 1957 to 7 March 1965)\n
•	Most consecutive league games without a loss away: 23, Barcelona (14 February 2010 to 30 April 2011)\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_records_team8">
Goals\n
Team\n
•	Most league goals scored in a season: 121, Real Madrid (2011–12)\n
•	Most home league goals scored in a season: 78, Real Madrid (1989–90)\n
•	Most away league goals scored in a season: 53, Real Madrid (2014-15)\n
•	Fewest league goals scored in a season: 15, Logroñés (1994–95)\n
    </string>

        <string name="la_liga_scorers">
1	Argentina	Lionel Messi	years:2004–present	311	goals\n
2	Portugal	Cristiano Ronaldo	years:2009–present	256	goals\n
3	Spain	Telmo Zarra	years:1940–1955	251	goals\n
4	Mexico	Hugo Sánchez	years:1981–1994	234	goals\n
5	Spain	Raúl	years:1994–2010	228	goals\n
6	Argentina	Alfredo di Stéfano	years:1953–1966	227	goals\n
7	Spain	César Rodríguez	years:1939–1955	223	goals\n
8	Spain	Quini	years:1970–1987	219	goals\n
9	Spain	Pahiño	years:1943–1956	210	goals\n
10	Spain	Edmundo Suárez	years:1939–1950	195	goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_history1">
The Premier League is an English professional league for men\'s association football clubs. At the top of the English football league system, it is the country\'s primary football competition. Contested by 20 clubs, it operates on a system of promotion and relegation with the Football League. Welsh clubs that compete in the English football league system can also qualify.\n
The Premier League is a corporation in which the 20 member clubs act as shareholders. Seasons run from August to May. Teams play 38 matches each (playing each team in the league twice, home and away), totalling 380 matches in the season. Most games are played on Saturday and Sunday afternoons; others during weekday evenings. It is currently sponsored by Barclays Bank and thus officially known as the Barclays Premier League and is colloquially known as the Premiership. Outside the UK it is commonly referred to as the English Premier League (EPL).\n
The competition formed as the FA Premier League on 20 February 1992 following the decision of clubs in the Football League First Division to break away from the Football League, which was originally founded in 1888, and take advantage of a lucrative television rights deal.\n
    </string>

      <string name="english_history_title1">
       History\n
    </string>

      <string name="english_history_title2">
        Origins\n
    </string>

      <string name="english_history2">
Despite significant European success in the 1970s and early 1980s, the late 80s marked a low point for English football.
Stadiums were crumbling, supporters endured poor facilities, hooliganism was rife, and English clubs banned from European competition for five years following the Heysel Stadium disaster in 1985.
The Football League First Division, the top level of English football since 1888, was behind leagues such as Italy\'s Serie A and Spain\'s La Liga in attendances and revenues, and several top English players had moved abroad.\n
By the turn of the 1990s the downward trend was starting to reverse: at the 1990 FIFA World Cup, England reached the semi-finals;
UEFA, European football\'s governing body, lifted the five-year ban on English clubs playing in European competitions in 1990, resulting in Manchester United lifting the UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup in 1991,
          and the Taylor Report on stadium safety standards, which proposed expensive upgrades to create all-seater stadiums in the aftermath of the Hillsborough disaster, was published in January of that year.\n
Television money also become more important: the Football League received £6.3 million for a two-year agreement in 1986, but when that deal was renewed in 1988, the price rose to £44 million over four years.
The 1988 negotiations were the first signs of a breakaway league: ten clubs threatened to leave and form a "super league",
          but were eventually persuaded to stay.As stadiums improved and match attendance and revenues rose, the country\'s top teams again considered leaving the Football League in order to capitalise on the influx of money into the sport.\n

    </string>

      <string name="english_history3">
At the close of the 1991 season, a proposal was tabled for the establishment of a new league that would bring more money into the game overall. The Founder Members Agreement,
          signed on 17 July 1991 by the game\'s top-flight clubs, established the basic principles for setting up the FA Premier League. The newly formed top division would have commercial independence from The Football Association and the Football League, giving the FA Premier League licence to negotiate its own broadcast and sponsorship agreements.\n
The argument given at the time was that the extra income would allow English clubs to compete with teams across Europe.
The managing director of London Weekend Television (LWT), Greg Dyke, met with the representatives of the "big five” football clubs in England in 1990. The meeting was to pave the way for a break away from The Football League.\n
Dyke believed that it would be more lucrative for LWT if only the larger clubs in the country were featured on national television and wanted to establish whether the clubs would be interested in a larger share of television rights money. The five clubs decided it was a good idea and decided to press ahead with it; however, the league would have no credibility without the backing of The Football Association and so David Dein of Arsenal held talks to see whether the FA were receptive to the idea.\n
The FA did not enjoy an amicable relationship with the Football League at the time and considered it as a way to weaken the Football League\'s position.\n
In 1992, the First Division clubs resigned from the Football League en masse and on 27 May 1992 the FA Premier League was formed as a limited company working out of an office at the Football Association's then headquarters in Lancaster Gate.\n
This meant a break-up of the 104-year-old Football League that had operated until then with four divisions; the Premier League would operate with a single division and the Football League with three. There was no change in competition format; the same number of teams competed in the top flight, and promotion and relegation between the Premier League and the new First Division remained the same as the old First and Second Divisions with three teams relegated from the league and three promoted.\n
The league held its first season in 1992–93 and was originally composed of 22 clubs. The first ever Premier League goal was scored by Brian Deane of Sheffield United in a 2–1 win against Manchester United.The 22 inaugural members of the new Premier League were Arsenal, Aston Villa, Blackburn Rovers, Chelsea, Coventry City,Crystal Palace, Everton, Ipswich Town, Leeds United, Liverpool, Manchester City, Manchester United, Middlesbrough, Norwich City, Nottingham Forest, Oldham Athletic,Queens Park Rangers, Sheffield United, Sheffield Wednesday, Southampton, Tottenham Hotspur, and Wimbledon. Luton Town, Notts County and West Ham Unitedwere the three teams relegated from the old first division at the end of the 1991–92 season, and did not take part in the inaugural Premier League season.\n
    </string>

 <string name="english_history4">
One significant feature of the Premier League in the mid 2000s was the dominance of "Big Four" clubs Arsenal, Chelsea, Liverpool and Manchester United. During this decade, and particularly from 2002 to 2009, they dominated the top four spots,
     which came with UEFA Champions League qualification, taking all top four places in 5 out of 6 seasons from 2003–04 to 2008–09 inclusive, with Arsenal going as far as winning the league without losing a single game in 2003–04,
     the only time it has ever happened in the Premier League. In May 2008 Kevin Keegan stated that "Big Four" dominance threatened the division, "This league is in danger of becoming one of the most boring but great leagues in the world. Premier League chief executive Richard Scudamore said in defence: There are a lot of different tussles that go on in the Premier League depending on whether you\'re at the top, in the middle or at the bottom that make it interesting.\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_history5">
The years following 2009 marked a shift in the structure of the "Big Four" with Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester City both breaking into the top four. In the 2009–10 season, Tottenham finished fourth and became the first team to break the top four since Everton in 2005. Criticism of the gap between an elite group of "super clubs" and the majority of the Premier League has continued, nevertheless, due to their increasing ability to spend more than the other Premier League clubs. Manchester City won the title in the 2011–12 season, becoming the first club outside the "Big Four" to win since 1994–95. That season also saw two of the Big Four (Chelsea and Liverpool) finish outside the top four places for the first time since 1994–95
    </string>


     <string name="english_records_title1">
       League\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records_title2">
       Titles\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records1">
•	Most League titles: 20, Manchester United\n
•	Most consecutive League titles: 3, joint record:\n
•	Huddersfield Town (1923–24, 1924–25, 1925–26)\n
•	Arsenal (1932–33, 1933–34, 1934–35)\n
•	Liverpool (1981–82, 1982–83, 1983–84)\n
•	Manchester United (twice): (1998–99, 1999–00, 2000–01) and (2006–07, 2007–08, 2008–09)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records_title3">
       Top-flight appearances\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records2">
•	Most consecutive seasons in top flight: 90 seasons, Arsenal (1919–present, though no League football was played due to second world war between 1939 and 1945–46;)\n
•	Most seasons in top flight overall: 113 seasons, Everton\n
•	Fewest seasons in top flight overall: 1 season, joint record, Glossop, Leyton Orient, Northampton, Carlisle United, Swindon and Barnsley have completed only one season in top flight in their history.\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records_title4">
       Wins\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records3">
•	Most wins overall: 2096, Manchester United\n
•	Most wins in the top-flight overall: 1803, Liverpool\n
•	Most wins at home overall: 1341, Manchester United\n
•	Most wins at home in top-flight overall: 1174, Everton\n
•	Most wins away overall: 755, Manchester United\n
•	Most wins away in top-flight overall: 638, Arsenal\n
•	Most wins in a season: 33, Doncaster Rovers (Third Division North, 1946–47; )\n
•	Most wins in a top flight season: 31, Tottenham Hotspur (First Division, 1960–61)\n
•	Most consecutive wins: 14, joint record:\n
•	Arsenal (Premier League between 10 February 2002 and 24 August 2002) (Top-flight record)\n
•	Manchester United (Second Division, 1904–05)\n
•	Bristol City (Second Division, 1905–06)\n
•	Preston North End (Second Division, 1950–51)\n
•	Most consecutive wins without conceding a goal: 9, Stockport County (League Two between January 13, 2007 and March 3, 2007)\n
•	Most consecutive home wins: 25, Bradford Park Avenue (Third Division North, 1926–27)\n
•	Most consecutive home wins top flight: 21, Liverpool (1972)\n
•	Most consecutive away wins in top flight: 12 Arsenal (Premier League between March 3, 2013 and October 26, 2013)\n
•	Fewest wins in a season: 1, joint record:\n
•	Derby County (Premier League, 2007–08))\n
•	Loughborough (Second Division, 1899–1900))\n
•	100%home win record in a season:\n
•	Sunderland (13 games; First Division, 1891–92)\n
•	Liverpool (14 games; Second Division, 1893–94)\n
•	Bury (15 games; Second Division, 1894–95)\n
•	Sheffield Wednesday (17 games; Second Division, 1899–1900)\n
•	Small Heath (17 games; Second Division, 1902–03)\n
•	Brentford (21 games; Third Division South, 1929–30)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_history_title5">
       Draws\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records4">
•	Most draws overall in the top flight: 1069, Everton\n
•	Most draws in a season: 23, joint record\n
•	Norwich City (from 42 games, First Division, 1978–79)\n
•	Exeter City (from 46 games, Fourth Division, 1986–87)\n
•	Hartlepool United (from 46 games, Third Division, 1997–98)\n
•	Cardiff City (from 46 games, Third Division, 1997–98)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_history_title6">
       Losses\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records5">
•	Most losses overall in the top flight: 1470, Everton\n
•	Most losses in a season: 34, Doncaster Rovers, (Third Division, 1997–98; )\n
•	Fewest losses: 0, joint record:\n
•	Preston North End (First Division, 1888–89; final record P22 W18 D4 L0)\n
•	Arsenal (Premier League, 2003–04; final record P38 W26 D12 L0)\n
•	Liverpool (Second Division, 1893-94; final record P28 W22 D6 L0)\n
•	Most consecutive losses\n
•	18, Darwen, 1898–1899 (Second Division)\n
•	17, Rochdale, 1931–32 (Division 3 North)\n
•	17, Sunderland, 2002-2003 (15 in top tier)\n

    </string>

     <string name="english_history_title7">
       Points\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records6">
•	Most points overall in the top flight: Liverpool\n
•	Most points in a season (2 points for a win): 74, Lincoln City (Fourth Division, 1975–76)\n
•	Most points in a season (3 points for a win): 106, Reading (Championship, 2005–06)\n
•	Most points in a season for a top-flight team (2 points for a win, 42 games): 68 (30 wins 8 draws), Liverpool (First Division, 1978–79)\n
•	Most points in a season for a top-flight team (3 points for a win, 38 games): 95 (29 wins 8 draws), Chelsea (Premier League, 2004–05)\n
•	Fewest points in a season (2 points for a win): 8, joint record:\n
•	Loughborough (Second Division, 1899–1900)\n
•	Doncaster Rovers (Second Division, 1904–05)\n
•	Fewest points in a season (3 points for a win): 11, Derby County (Premier League, 2007–08)\n
•	Most points in a season while being relegated (3 points for a win): 54, joint record:\n
•	Southend United (Third Division, 21st of 24; 1988–89)\n
•	Peterborough United (Championship, 22nd of 24; 2012-13\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_history_title8">
       Goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_records7">
•	Most league goals scored in a season: (134) Peterborough United (Fourth Division, 1960–61)\n
•	Most top-flight goals scored in a season (42 games): 128, Aston Villa (First Division, 1930–31)\n
•	Most top flight goals scored in total: 6699, Everton.\n
•	Most home league goals scored in a season: 87, Millwall (Third Division South, 1927–28)\n
•	Most away league goals scored in a season: 60, Arsenal (First Division, 1930–31)\n
•	Most consecutive games scoring: 55, Arsenal (Premier League 19 May 2001 – 30 November 2002)\n
•	Most consecutive games without scoring: 11, Coventry\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_records8">
•	Most titles won by an individual player: 13, Ryan Giggs\n
•	Most career league appearances: 1,005 (849 in First Division), Peter Shilton (1966 to 1997)\n
•	Most career league appearances by an outfield player: 931, Tony Ford (1975 to 2002)\n
•	Most career league appearances at one club: 770, John Trollope (Swindon Town, 1960 to 1980)\n
•	Most career top flight league appearances at one club: 672, Ryan Giggs (Manchester United, 1991 to 6 May 2014)\n
•	Most career consecutive league appearances: 375, Harold Bell (Tranmere Rovers), 1946 to 1955 (401 consecutive club games including 26 FA Cup appearances)\n
•	Oldest player: Neil McBain, 51 years and 20 days (for New Brighton v. Hartlepool United, 1947)\n
•	Youngest player: Reuben Noble-Lazarus, 15 years and 45 days (for Barnsley v. Ipswich Town, 30 September 2008)\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_history_title9">
       Goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_records9">
•	Most career league goals: 434, Arthur Rowley (619 matches, for West Bromwich Albion, Fulham, Leicester City and Shrewsbury Town, 1946 to 1965)\n
•	Most career top-flight goals: 357, Jimmy Greaves (516 matches, for Chelsea, Tottenham Hotspur and West Ham United, 1957 to 1971)\n
•	Most consecutive top flight league matches scored in: 12, Jimmy Dunne, for Sheffield United between 24-October-1931 and 1-January-1932, 18 goals in all.\n
•	Most goals in a season: 60, Dixie Dean (39 matches, for Everton 1927–28)\n
•	Most goals in a game: 10, Joe Payne (for Luton Town v. Bristol Rovers, 13 April 1936)\n
•	Most goals in a top flight game: 7, Ted Drake for Arsenal v. Aston Villa (away), 14 December 1935\n
•	Fastest goal: 3.5 seconds, Colin Cowperthwaite (for Barrow v. Kettering Town, 1979)\n
•	Fastest goal on a League debut: 7 seconds, Freddy Eastwood (for Southend United v. Swansea City, 16 October 2004)\n
•	Fastest hat-trick (time between first and third goals): 2 minutes 20 seconds, James Hayter (for AFC Bournemouth v. Wrexham, 23 February 2004)\n
•	Fastest goal by a substitute: 1.8 seconds, Nicklas Bendtner (for Arsenal v. Tottenham Hotspur, 22 December 2007)\n
•	Most own goals in one season: 5, Bobby Stuart (Middlesbrough, 1934–35)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records10">
1	  Alan Shearer Blackburn Rovers, Newcastle United 260 goals\n
2	  Wayne Rooney Everton, Manchester United 192 goals\n
3	  Andy Cole Newcastle United, Manchester United, Blackburn Rovers, Fulham, Manchester City,Portsmouth 187 goals\n
4	  Frank Lampard West Ham United, Chelsea, Manchester City 177 goals\n
5	  Thierry Henry Arsenal 175 goals\n
6	  Robbie Fowler Liverpool, Leeds United, Manchester City 163 goals\n
7	  Michael Owen Liverpool, Newcastle United, Manchester United, Stoke City 150 goals\n
8	  Les Ferdinand Queens Park Rangers, Newcastle United, Tottenham Hotspur, West Ham United,Leicester City, Bolton Wanderers 149 goals\n
9	  Teddy Sheringham Nottingham Forest, Tottenham Hotspur, Manchester United, Portsmouth, West Ham United 146 goals\n
10	  Robin van Persie Arsenal, Manchester United 144 goals
    </string>

    <string name="german_history_1">
      The Bundesliga is a professional association football league in Germany and the football league with the highest average stadium attendance worldwide. At the top of the German football league system, the Bundesliga is Germany\'s primary football competition.
        The Bundesliga is contested by 18 teams and operates on a system of promotion and relegation with the 2. Bundesliga. Seasons run from August to May. Most games are played on Saturdays and Sundays, with a few games played on weekdays. All of the Bundesliga clubs qualify for the DFB-Pokal. The winner of the Bundesliga qualifies for the DFL-Supercup.\n
A total of 53 clubs have competed in the Bundesliga since its founding. FC Bayern Munich has won the Bundesliga the most, winning the title 24 times. However, the Bundesliga has seen other champions with Borussia Dortmund, Hamburger SV, Werder Bremen, Borussia Mönchengladbach and VfB Stuttgart most prominent among them. The Bundesliga is one of the top national leagues, currently ranked 2nd in Europe according to UEFA\'s league coefficient ranking, based on performances in European competitions over the past five seasons.\n
        The Bundesliga is the number one football league in the world in terms of average attendance; out of all sports, its average of 45,134 fans per game during the 2011–12 season was the second highest of any sports league in the world after the National Football League. The Bundesliga is broadcast on television in over 200 countries.
The Bundesliga was founded in 1962 in Dortmund and the first season started in 1963. The structure and organisation of the Bundesliga along with Germany\'s other football leagues have undergone frequent changes right up to the present day.
        The Bundesliga was originally founded by the Deutscher Fußball-Bund (English: German Football Association), but is now operated by the Deutsche Fußball Liga (English: German Football League).

    </string>

    <string name="german_history_title1">
       History\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_history_title2">
       Origins\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_history_2">
       Prior to the formation of the Bundesliga, German football was played at an amateur level in a large number of sub-regional leagues until, in 1949, part-time (semi-) professionalism was introduced and only five regional Oberligen (Premier Leagues) remained.\n
        Regional champions and runners-up played a series of playoff matches for the right to compete in a final game for the national championship. On 28 January 1900, a national association, the Deutscher Fußball Bund (DFB) had been founded in Leipzig with 86 member clubs. The first recognised national championship team was VfB Leipzig, who beat DFC Prague 7–2 in a game played at Altona on 31 May 1903.\n
Through the 1950s, there were continued calls for the formation of a central professional league, especially as professional leagues in other countries began to draw Germany\'s best players away from the semi-professional domestic leagues. At the international level the German game began to falter as German teams often fared poorly against professional teams from other countries.\n
        A key supporter of the central league concept was national team head coach Sepp Herberger who said, “If we want to remain competitive internationally, we have to raise our expectations at the national level.”\n
Meanwhile, in East Germany, a separate league was established with the formation of the DS-Oberliga (Deutscher Sportausschuss Oberliga) in 1950.
        The league was renamed the Football Oberliga DFV in 1958 and was generally referred to simply as the DDR-Liga or DDR-Oberliga. The league fielded 14 teams with two relegation spots.\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_history_title3">
       Foundation\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_history_3">
       The Bundesliga was founded at the annual DFB convention at the Westfalenhallen in Dortmund on 28 July 1962
The defeat of the national team by Yugoslavia (0–1) in a 1962 World Cup quarter-final game in Chile was one impetus (of many) towards the formation of a national league. At the annual DFB convention under new DFB president Hermann Gösmann (elected that very day) the Bundesliga was created in Dortmund at the Westfalenhallen on 28 July 1962 to begin play starting with the 1963–64 season.\n
At the time, there were five Oberligen (Premier Leagues) in place representing West Germany\'s North, South, West, Southwest, and Berlin. East Germany, behind the Iron Curtain, maintained its separate league structure. 46 clubs applied for admission to the new league. 16 teams were selected based on their success on the field, economic criteria and representation of the various Oberligen.\n
    </string>


    <string name="german_records_title1">
       Club records\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title2">
       Titles\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records1">
       Highest number of titles won: 24by Bayern Munich (1968–69, 1971–72 to 1973–74, 1979–80, 1980–81, 1984–85 to 1986–87, 1988–89, 1989–90, 1993–94,1996–97, 1998–99 to 2000–01, 2002–03, 2004–05, 2005–06, 2007–08, 2009–10, 2012–13 to 2014–15)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title3">
       Champions\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records2">
•	Highest number of games left when becoming champions: 7 by Bayern Munich (2013–14)\n
•	Earliest point of time in a year for a team to be crowned champions: 25 March by Bayern Munich (2013–14)\n
•	Highest number of matchdays being league leaders: 708 by Bayern Munich\n
•	Highest number of matchdays being league leaders in a season: 34 by Bayern Munich (1968–69, 1972–73, 1984–85 2007–08 and 2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of matchdays being league leaders in a season for the champions: 1 by Bayern Munich (1985–86)\n
•	Lowest number of seasons before becoming champions after being promoted: 1 by 1. FC Kaiserslautern (Promotion: 1997; Champions: 1997–98)\n
•	Lowest number of seasons before getting relegated for the champions: 1 by 1. FC Nürnberg (Champions: 1967–68; Relegation: 1968–69)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title4">
       Points\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records3">
•	Highest number of points in a season: 91 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of points in a season opening half: 47 by Bayern Munich (2013–14)\n
•	Highest number of points in a season closing half: 49 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of points in a season away: 47 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of points in a season at home: 49 by FC Schalke 04 (33:1) (1971–72), Bayern Munich (33:1) (1972–73) and VfL Wolfsburg (2008–09)\n
•	Highest percentage of total possible points in a season: 89.22 by Bayern Munich (2012–13) (91 points out of a possible 102)\n
•	Highest percentage of total possible points in a season opening half: 92.16 by Bayern Munich (2013–14) (47 points out of a possible 51)\n
•	Highest percentage of total possible points in a season closing half: 96.08 by Bayern Munich (2012–13) (49 points out of a possible 51)\n
•	Highest percentage of total possible points in a season at home: 96.08 by FC Schalke 04 (1971–72), Bayern Munich (1972–73) and VfL Wolfsburg (2008–09) (49 points out of a possible 51) (Based on 16 wins and a draw with 3 points per win)\n
•	Highest percentage of total possible points in a season away: 92.16 by Bayern Munich (2012–13) (47 points out of a possible 51)\n
•	Biggest lead in points after a season opening half: 11 by Bayern Munich (45) upon VfL Wolfsburg (34) (2014-15)\n
•	Biggest margin of points between champions and runner-up: 25 between Bayern Munich (91) and Borussia Dortmund (66) (2012–13)\n
•	Highest percentage of points difference between champions and runner-up: 27.47 between Bayern Munich (91) and Borussia Dortmund (66) (2012–13)\n
•	Highest points per game average: 1.98 by Bayern Munich\n
•	Highest points per game average in a season: 2.68 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of points in a season: 10 by Tasmania Berlin (8:60) (1965–66)\n
•	Lowest number of points in a season opening half: 4 by Tasmania Berlin (3:31) (1965–66)\n
•	Lowest number of points in a season closing half: 4 by Hannover 96 (4:30) (1985–86)\n
•	Lowest number of points in a season away: 0 by 1. FC Nürnberg (1983–84)\n
•	Lowest number of points in a season at home: 4 by SpVgg Greuther Fürth (2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of points in a calendar year: 93 by Bayern Munich (2013)\n
•	Highest percentage of total possible points in a calendar year: 93.94 by Bayern Munich (2013) (93 points out of a possible 99)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title5">
       Wins and losses\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records4">
•	Highest number of wins: 1015 by Bayern Munich\n
•	Highest number of wins in a season: 29 by Bayern Munich (2012–13 and 2013–14)\n
•	Highest number of wins in a season opening half: 15 by Bayern Munich (2013–14 and 2015–16)\n
•	Highest number of wins in a season closing half: 16 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of wins in a season away: 15 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of losses in a season: 1 by Bayern Munich (1986–87 and 2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of losses in a season opening half:0 by Hamburger SV (1982–83), Bayern Munich (1988–89, 2013–14 and 2014–15) and Bayer Leverkusen(2009–10)\n
•	Lowest number of losses in a season closing half:0 by Eintracht Frankfurt (1976–77), Bayern Munich (1986–87 and 2012–13) and Borussia Dortmund (2011–12)\n
•	Highest number of losses: 607 by Eintracht Frankfurt\n
•	Highest number of losses in a season 28 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of losses in a season opening half: 15 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of losses in a season closing half: 13 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66) and FC St. Pauli (1996–97)\n
•	Highest number of losses in a season at home: 13 by SpVgg Greuther Fürth (2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of losses in a season away: 17 by 1. FC Nürnberg (1983–84)\n
•	Lowest number of wins in a season: 2 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66) and Wuppertaler SV (1974–75)\n
•	Lowest number of wins in a season opening half: 0 by 1. FC Nürnberg (2013–14)\n
•	Lowest number of wins in a season closing half: 0 by Wuppertaler SV (1974–75) and Hannover 96 (1985–86)\n
•	Lowest number of wins in a season at home: 0 by SpVgg Greuther Fürth (2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of wins in a season away: 0 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66), Karlsruher SC (1965–66, 1967–68 and 1976–77), Borussia Neunkirchen (1967–68),Borussia Dortmund (1967–68 and 1978–79), Hannover 96 (1969–70 and 1971–72), Alemannia Aachen (1969–70), Arminia Bielefeld (1971–72), Rot-Weiß Oberhausen (1972–73), Hertha Berlin (1972–73 and 1982–83) Wuppertaler SV (1974–75), VfB Stuttgart (1974–75 and 2000–01), VfL Bochum (1975–76), Tennis Borussia Berlin (1976–77), Rot-Weiß Essen (1976–77), Bayern Munich (1977–78), Eintracht Braunschweig (1979–80), Bayer 05 Uerdingen (1980–81), Fortuna Düsseldorf (1981–82),\n
 MSV Duisburg (1981–82), 1. FC Nürnberg (1983–84), Kickers Offenbach (1983–84), Eintracht Frankfurt (1986–87 and 1995–96), FC 08 Homburg (1986–87), SV Waldhof Mannheim (1986–87), FC St. Pauli (1988–89 and 2001–02), Dynamo Dresden (1992–93), SG Wattenscheid 09 (1993–94), Borussia Mönchengladbach (1998–99 and 2004–05), 1. FC Köln (2003–04) and SC Freiburg (2003–04)\n
•	Highest winning percentage: 58.54 by Bayern Munich (1015 wins in 1734 games)\n
•	Highest losing percentage: 82.35 by Tasmania Berlin (28 losses in 34 games)\n
•	Highest percentage of wins in a season: 85.29 by Bayern Munich (2012–13 and 2013–14) (29 wins in 34 games)\n
•	Highest percentage of wins in a season opening half: 88.24 by Bayern Munich (2013–14 and 2015–16) (15 wins in 17 games)\n
•	Highest percentage of wins in a season closing half: 94.12 by Bayern Munich (2012–13) (16 wins in 17 games)\n
•	Highest number of wins in a debut season: 20 by Bayern Munich (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of wins in a calendar year: 30 by Bayern Munich (2013)\n
•	Highest percentage of wins in a calendar year: 90.90 by Bayern Munich (2013) (30 wins in 33 games)\n
•	Lowest number of losses in a calendar year: 0 by Bayern Munich (2013)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title6">
       Goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records5">
•	Highest number of scored goals in a season: 101 by Bayern Munich (1971–72)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a season opening half: 50 by Hamburger SV (1981–82)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a season closing half: 54 by Bayern Munich (1971–72 and 2012–13)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a season at home: 69 by Bayern Munich (1971–72)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a season away: 46 by Bayern Munich (2013–14)\n
•	Lowest number of conceded goals in a season: 18 by Bayern Munich (2012–13 and 2014–15)\n
•	Lowest number of conceded goals in a season away: 7 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of conceded goals in a season at home: 5 by Werder Bremen (1992–93)\n
•	Lowest number of conceded goals in a season opening half: 4 by Bayern Munich (2014–15)\n
•	Lowest number of conceded goals in a season closing half: 10 by Borussia Mönchengladbach (2014–15)\n
•	Best goal difference in a season: +80 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Best goal difference in a season away: +38 by Bayern Munich (2013–14)\n
•	Best goal difference in a season at home: +49 by Bayern Munich (1972–73)\n
•	Best goal difference in a season opening half: +38 by Bayern Munich (2015–16)\n
•	Best goal difference in a season closing half: +43 by Bayern Munich (2012–13)\n
•	Lowest number of scored goals in a season: 15 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Lowest number of scored goals in a season away: 7 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Lowest number of scored goals in a season at home: 8 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Lowest number of scored goals in a season opening half: 8 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66) and Eintracht Frankfurt (1988–89)\n
•	Lowest number of scored goals in a season closing half: 7 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of conceded goals in a season: 108 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of conceded goals in a season away: 70 by Kickers Offenbach (1983–84)\n
•	Highest number of conceded goals in a season at home: 46 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of conceded goals in a season opening half: 58 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Highest number of conceded goals in a season closing half: 53 by Kickers Offenbach and Fortuna Düsseldorf (both 1983–84)\n
•	Worst goal difference in a season: -93 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Worst goal difference in a season away: -55 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66) and Kickers Offenbach (1983–84)\n
•	Worst goal difference in a season at home: -38 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Worst goal difference in a season opening half: -50 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
•	Worst goal difference in a season closing half: -43 by Tasmania Berlin (1965–66)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title7">
       Player records\n
    </string>

     <string name="german_records_title8">
       Championships\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records6">
•	Highest number of won championships overall: 8 by Udo Lattek (1971–72 to 1973–74, 1984–85 to 1986–87 with Bayern Munich and 1975–76 and 1976–77 withBorussia Mönchengladbach), Mehmet Scholl (1993–94, 1996–97, 1998–99 to 2000–01, 2002–03, 2004–05 and 2005–06 with Bayern Munich), Oliver Kahn (1996–97,1998–99 to 2000–01, 2002–03, 2004–05, 2005–06 and 2007–08 with Bayern Munich) and Bastian Schweinsteiger (2002–03, 2004–05, 2005–06, 2007–08, 2009–10and 2012–13 to 2014–15 with Bayern Munich)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_title9">
       Goals\n
    </string>

     <string name="german_records7">
•	Highest number of scored goals: 365 by Gerd Müller\n
•	Highest number of scored goals for one club: 365 by Gerd Müller for Bayern Munich\n
•	Highest number of scored goals for one club, playing for no other club: 365 by Gerd Müller for Bayern Munich\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a season: 40 by Gerd Müller for Bayern Munich (1971–72)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a game: 6 by Dieter Müller for 1. FC Köln (matchday 3 of 1977–78)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals in a game by a substitute: 5 by Robert Lewandowski for Bayern Munich (matchday 6 of 2015–16)\n
•	Highest number of topscorer awards: 7 by Gerd Müller for Bayern Munich (1966–67, 1968–69, 1969–70, 1971–72 to 1973–74 and 1977–78)\n
•	Highest number of scored goals by a foreign player: 189 by Claudio Pizarro for Werder Bremen and Bayern Munich (1999 to 2007 and 2008 to 2016)\n
•	Shortest elapsed timespan before a scored goal: 9 seconds by: Karim Bellarabi for Bayer Leverkusen (matchday 1 of 2014–15) and Kevin Volland for 1899 Hoffenheim (matchday 2 of 2015–16)\n
    </string>

    <string name="german_records_10">
1	Gerd Müller Bayern München games 427	goals 365\n
2	Klaus Fischer TSV 1860 München FC Schalke 04 FC Köln VfL Bochum games 535	goals 268\n
3	Jupp Heynckes Hannover 96 Bor. Mönchengladbach games 369	goals 220\n
4	Manfred Burgsmüller Werder Bremen Borussia Dortmund FC NürnbergRot-Weiss Essen games 447	goals 213\n
5	Claudio Pizarro Werder Bremen Bayern München games 409	goals 190\n
6	Ulf Kirsten Bayer Leverkusen games 350	goals 182\n
7	Stefan Kuntz FC KaiserslauternArminia BielefeldVfL Bochum KFC Uerdingen 05 games 449	goals 179\n
8	Klaus Allofs Werder BremenFC Köln Fortuna Düsseldorf games 424	goals 177\n
9	Dieter Müller FC Saarbrücken FC KölnVfB Stuttgart games 303	goals 177\n
10	Hannes Löhr FC Köln games 381	goals 166
    </string>

      <string name="mls_history1">
Major League Soccer (MLS) is a men\’s professional soccer league, sanctioned by U.S. Soccer, that represents the sport\'s highest level in both the United States and Canada. MLS is sometimes considered one of the major professional sports leagues of the United States and Canada.\n
The league is composed of 20 teams—17 in the U.S. and 3 in Canada. The MLS regular season runs from March to October, with each team playing 34 games; the team with the best record is awarded the Supporters Shield. The post season includes twelve teams competing in the MLS Cup Playoffs through November and December, culminating in the championship game, the MLS Cup.MLS teams also play in other domestic competitions against teams from other divisions in the U.S.\n
Open Cup and in the Canadian Championship. MLS teams also compete against continental rivals in the CONCACAF Champions League.
Major League Soccer was founded in 1993 as part of the United States successful bid to host the 1994 FIFA World Cup.\n
The first season took place in 1996 with ten teams. MLS experienced financial and operational struggles in its first few years: The league lost millions of dollars, teams played in mostly empty American football stadiums, and two teams folded in 2002. Since then, MLS has expanded to 20 teams, owners built soccer-specific stadiums, average MLS attendance exceeds that of the National Hockey League(NHL) and National Basketball Association (NBA),
MLS secured national TV contracts, and the league is now profitable.
</string>

 <string name="mls_history4">
Instead of operating as an association of independently owned teams, MLS is a single entity in which each team is owned and controlled by the league\’s investors.
The investor-operators control their teams as owners control teams in other leagues, and are commonly (but inaccurately) referred to as the team\'s owners. The league has a fixed membership, like most sports leagues in the United States and Canada, which makes it one of the world\'s few soccer leagues that does not use promotion and relegation, a practice that is uncommon in the two countries. MLS headquarters is located in New York City.\n
Major League Soccer\’s regular season runs from March to October. Teams are divided into the Eastern and Western Conferences. Teams play 34 games in an unbalanced schedule: 24 matches against teams within their conference, plus 10 matches against teams from the other conference.Midway through the season, teams break for the annual All-Star Game, a friendly game between the league\'s finest players and a major club from a different league.
At the end of the regular season, the team with the highest point total is awarded the Supporters Shield.\n
Unlike other soccer leagues around the world, the MLS regular season is followed by the 12-team MLS Cup Playoffs in November, ending with the MLS Cup championship final in early December.
Although some commentators have argued that playoffs reduce the importance of the regular season, Commissioner Don Garber has explained "Our purpose is to have a valuable competition, and that includes having playoffs that are more meaningful.
Major League Soccer\’s spring-to-autumn schedule results in scheduling conflicts with the FIFA calendar and with summertime international tournaments such as the World Cup and the Gold Cup, causing several players to miss some MLS matches.
While MLS has looked into changing to an autumn-to-spring format, there are no current plans to do so. If the league were to change its schedule, a winter break would be needed, especially with several teams in colder climates, which some believe would lead to a disadvantage. It would also have to compete with the more popular National Football League (NFL), National Hockey League (NHL), andNational Basketball Association (NBA).\n
      </string>

      <string name="mls_title1">
       History\n
    </string>

      <string name="mls_history2">
   Major League Soccer is the most recent of a series of men\’s premier professional national soccer leagues established in the United States and Canada.
   The predecessor of MLS was the North American Soccer League (NASL), which played from 1968 until 1984.\n
    </string>
      <string name="mls_title2">
       Establishment\n
    </string>
      <string name="mls_history3">
In 1988, in exchange for FIFA awarding the right to host the 1994 World Cup, U.S. Soccer promised to establish a Division 1 professional soccer league. In 1993, U.S. Soccer selected Major League Professional Soccer (the precursor to MLS) as the exclusive Division 1 professional soccer league. Major League Soccer was officially formed in February 1995 as a limited liability company.\n
MLS began play in 1996 with ten teams. The first game was held on April 6, 1996, as the San Jose Clash defeated D.C. United before 31,000 fans at Spartan Stadium in San Jose in a game broadcast on ESPN. The league had generated some buzz by managing to lure some marquee players from the 1994 World Cup to play in MLS—including U.S. stars such as Alexi Lalas, Tony Meola and Eric Wynalda, and foreign players such as Mexico\’s Jorge Campos and Colombia\'s Carlos Valderrama. D.C. United won the MLS Cup in three of the league\’s first four seasons.
The league added its first two expansion teams in 1998—the Miami Fusion and the Chicago Fire; the Chicago Fire won its first title in its inaugural season.
After its first season, MLS suffered from a decline in attendance. The league\’s low attendance was all the more apparent in light of the fact that eight of the original ten teams played in large American football stadiums. One aspect that had alienated fans was that MLS experimented with rules deviations in its early years in an attempt to "Americanize" the sport. The league implemented the use of shootouts to resolve tie games.MLS also used a countdown clock and halves ended when the clock reached 0:00.\n
The league realized that the rule changes had alienated some traditional soccer fans while failing to draw new American sports fans, and the shootout and countdown clock were eliminated after the 1999 season. The league\’s quality was cast into doubt when the U.S. men\'s national team, which was made up largely of MLS players, finished in last place at the 1998 World Cup.
Major League Soccer lost an estimated $250 million during its first five years, and more than $350 million between its founding and 2004. The league\'s financial problems led to Commissioner Doug Logan being replaced by Garber, a former NFL executive, in August 1999. MLS announced in January 2002 that it had decided to contract the Tampa Bay Mutiny and Miami Fusion, leaving the league with ten teams.
Despite the financial problems, though, MLS did have some accomplishments that would set the stage for the league\’s resurgence. Columbus Crew Stadium was built in 1999, becoming MLS\’s first soccer-specific stadium. This began a trend among MLS teams to construct their own venues instead of leasing American football stadiums. In 2000, the league won an antitrust lawsuit, Fraser v. Major League Soccer, that the players had filed in 1996. The court ruled that MLS\’s policy of centrally contracting players and limiting player salaries through a salary cap and other restrictions were a legal method for the league to maintain solvency and competitive parity.
    </string>
      <string name="mls_records">
1	United States Landon Donovan	games 144	goals 334\n
2	United States Jeff Cunningham	games 134	goals 365\n
3	Bolivia Jaime Moreno	games 133	goals 340\n
4	United States Chris Wondolowski	games 116	goals 237\n
5	United States Ante Razov	games 114	goals 262\n
6	United States Jason Kreis	games 108	goals 305\n
7	Canada Dwayne De Rosario	games 104	goals 343\n
8	United States Taylor Twellman	games 101	goals 174\n
9	United States Edson Buddle	games 100	goals 304\n
10	United States Roy Lassiter	games 88	goals 179\n
10	Guatemala Carlos Ruiz	games 88	goals 182\n
    </string>


    <string name="nba_records_title">
        RECORDS\n
    </string>

          <string name="nba_records">
•	Most minutes in a game\n
	•	69 by Dale Ellis, Seattle SuperSonics (at Milwaukee Bucks) on November 9, 1989 (5 OT)\n
	•	Most points in a game\n
	•	100 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962\n
	•	Most points in a half\n
	•	59 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962 (2nd)\n
	•	Most points in a quarter\n
	•	37 by Klay Thompson, Golden State Warriors (vs. Sacramento Kings) on January 23, 2015 (3rd)\n
	•	Most points in an overtime period\n
	•	16 by Gilbert Arenas, Washington Wizards (vs. Los Angeles Lakers) on December 17, 2006\n
    </string>

    <string name="nba_records1">
    •	Most field goals made in a game\n
	•	36 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962\n
	•	Most field goals attempted in a game\n
	•	63 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962\n
	•	Most field goals missed in a game\n
	•	30 by Kobe Bryant, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Boston Celtics) on November 7, 2002\n
	•	Most field goals made in a half\n
	•	22 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962 (2nd)\n
	•	Most field goals attempted in a half\n
	•	37 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962 (2nd)\n
	•	Most field goals made in a quarter\n
	•	13 by David Thompson, Denver Nuggets (vs. Detroit Pistons) on April 9, 1978 (1st)\n
	•	13 by Klay Thompson, Golden State Warriors (vs. Sacramento Kings) on January 23, 2015 (3rd)\n
	•	Most field goals attempted in a quarter\n
	•	21 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962 (4th)\n
	•	Most field goals made in a game, no misses\n
	•	18 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia 76ers (vs. Baltimore Bullets) on February 24, 1967\n
	•	Most field goals attempted in a game, none made\n
	•	17 by Tim Hardaway, Golden State Warriors (at Minnesota Timberwolves) on December 27, 1991\n
	•	Most 3-point field goals made in a game\n
	•	12 by Kobe Bryant, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Seattle SuperSonics) on January 7, 2003 \n
	•	12 by Donyell Marshall, Toronto Raptors (vs. Philadelphia 76ers) on March 13, 2005 \n
	•	12 by Stephen Curry, Golden State Warriors (vs. Oklahoma City Thunder) on February 27, 2016\n
	•	Most 3-point field goals attempted in a game\n
	•	22 by J. R. Smith, New York Knicks (at Miami Heat) on April 6, 2014 \n
	•	Most 3-point field goals made in a half\n
	•	10 by Chandler Parsons, Houston Rockets (vs. Memphis Grizzlies) on January 24, 2014\n
	•	Most 3-point field goals made in a quarter\n
	•	9 by Klay Thompson, Golden State Warriors (vs. Sacramento Kings) on January 23, 2015 (9-9)\n
	•	Most 3-point field goals made in a game, no misses\n
	•	9 by Latrell Sprewell, New York Knicks (vs. Los Angeles Clippers) on February 4, 2003\n
	•	9 by Ben Gordon, Chicago Bulls (vs. Washington Wizards) on April 14, 2006\n
	•	9 by Ben Gordon, Detroit Pistons (at Denver Nuggets) on March 21, 2012\n
	•	Most consecutive 3-point field goals made to start a game\n
	•	10 by Ty Lawson, Denver Nuggets (vs. Minnesota Timberwolves) on April 9, 2011\n
	•	Most 3-point field goals attempted in a game, none made\n
	•	11 by Antoine Walker, Boston Celtics (vs. Philadelphia 76ers) on December 17, 2001\n
	•	11 by Trey Burke, Utah Jazz (vs. Atlanta Hawks) on January 2, 2015\n
	•	Most free throws made in a game\n
	•	28 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. New York Knicks) on March 2, 1962 (28-32)\n
	•	28 by Adrian Dantley, Utah Jazz (vs. Houston Rockets) on January 4, 1984 (28-29)\n
	•	Most free throws made in a game, no misses\n
	•	23 by Dominique Wilkins, Atlanta Hawks (vs. Chicago Bulls) on December 8, 1992\n
	•	Most free throws attempted in a game, none made\n
	•	11 by Shaquille O\'Neal, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Seattle SuperSonics) on December 8, 2000\n
	•	Most free throws attempted in a game\n
	•	39 by Dwight Howard, Orlando Magic (vs. Golden State Warriors) on January 12, 2012 (21-39)\n
	•	39 by Dwight Howard, Los Angeles Lakers (at Orlando Magic) on March 12, 2013 (25-39)\n
	•	Most free throws missed in a game\n
	•	23 by Andre Drummond, Detroit Pistons (at Houston Rockets) on January 20, 2016 (13-36)\n
	•	Most free throws made in a half\n
	•	20 by Michael Jordan, Chicago Bulls (vs. Miami Heat) on December 30, 1992\n
	•	Most free throws attempted in a half\n
	•	26 by Josh Smith, Houston Rockets (vs. San Antonio Spurs) on April 10, 2015 (12-26)\n
	•	Most free throws made in a quarter\n
	•	16 by Vince Carter, New Jersey Nets (at Miami Heat) on December 23, 2005\n
	•	Most free throws attempted in a quarter\n
	•	20 by Ben Wallace, Detroit Pistons (at Los Angeles Clippers) on December 11, 2005\n
	•	Most rebounds in a game\n
	•	55 by Wilt Chamberlain, Philadelphia Warriors (vs. Boston Celtics) on November 24, 1960\n
	•	Most rebounds in a half\n
	•	32 by Bill Russell, Boston Celtics (vs. Philadelphia Warriors) on November 16, 1957\n
	•	Most rebounds in a quarter\n
	•	18 by Nate Thurmond, San Francisco Warriors (at Baltimore Bullets) on February 28, 1965\n
	•	Most offensive rebounds in a game\n
	•	21 by Moses Malone, Houston Rockets (vs. Seattle SuperSonics) on February 11, 1982\n
	•	Most defensive rebounds in a game\n
	•	29 by Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Detroit Pistons) on December 14, 1975\n
	•	Most offensive rebounds in a half\n
	•	13 by Charles Barkley, Philadelphia 76ers (vs. New York Knicks) on March 4, 1987\n
	•	Most defensive rebounds in a half\n
	•	13 by Swen Nater, San Diego Clippers (vs. Denver Nuggets) on December 14, 1979\n
	•	Most offensive rebounds in a quarter\n
	•	11 by Charles Barkley, Philadelphia 76ers (vs. New York Knicks) on March 4, 1987\n
	•	11 by Larry Smith, Golden State Warriors (vs. Denver Nuggets) on March 23, 1986\n
	•	Most defensive rebounds in a quarter\n
	•	13 by Happy Hairston, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Philadelphia 76ers) on November 15, 1974\n
	•	Most assists in a game\n
	•	30 by Scott Skiles, Orlando Magic (vs. Denver Nuggets) on December 30, 1990\n
	•	Most assists in a half\n
	•	19 by Bob Cousy, Boston Celtics (vs. Minneapolis Lakers) on February 27, 1959\n
	•	Most assists in a quarter\n
	•	14 by John Lucas, San Antonio Spurs (vs. Denver Nuggets) on April 15, 1984\n
	•	14 by Steve Blake, Portland Trail Blazers (vs. Los Angeles Clippers) on February 22, 2009\n
	•	Most steals in a game\n
	•	11 by Larry Kenon, San Antonio Spurs (at Kansas City Kings) on December 26, 1976\n
	•	11 by Kendall Gill, New Jersey Nets (vs. Miami Heat) on April 3, 1999\n
	•	Most steals in a half\n
	•	8 by Quinn Buckner, Milwaukee Bucks (vs. New York Nets) on November 27, 1976\n
	•	8 by Fred Brown, Seattle SuperSonics (at Philadelphia 76ers) on December 3, 1976\n
	•	8 by Gus Williams, Seattle SuperSonics (at Washington Bullets) on January 23, 1979\n
	•	8 by Eddie Jordan, New Jersey Nets (at Chicago Bulls) on October 23, 1979\n
	•	8 by Dudley Bradley, Indiana Pacers (at Utah Jazz) on November 10, 1980\n
	•	8 by Rob Williams, Denver Nuggets (at New Jersey Nets) on February 17, 1983\n
	•	8 by Fat Lever, Denver Nuggets (vs. Indiana Pacers) on March 9, 1985\n
	•	8 by Michael Jordan, Chicago Bulls (at Boston Celtics) on November 9, 1988\n
	•	8 by Clyde Drexler, Houston Rockets (vs. Sacramento Kings) on November 1, 1996\n
	•	8 by Doug Christie, Toronto Raptors (at Philadelphia 76ers) on April 2, 1997\n
	•	8 by Michael Finley, Dallas Mavericks (vs. Philadelphia 76ers) on January 23, 2001\n
	•	8 by Rafer Alston, Houston Rockets (vs. Charlotte Bobcats) on February 10, 2007\n
	•	Most steals in a quarter\n
	•	8 by Fat Lever, Denver Nuggets (vs. Indiana Pacers) on March 9, 1985\n
	•	Most blocks in a game\n
	•	17 by Elmore Smith, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Portland Trail Blazers) on October 28, 1973\n
	•	Most blocks in a half\n
	•	11 by Elmore Smith, Los Angeles Lakers (vs. Portland Trail Blazers) on October 28, 1973\n
	•	11 by George T. Johnson, San Antonio Spurs (vs. Golden State Warriors) on February 24, 1981\n
	•	11 by Manute Bol, Washington Bullets (vs. Milwaukee Bucks) on December 12, 1985\n
	•	Most blocks in a quarter\n
	•	8 by Manute Bol, Washington Bullets (vs. Milwaukee Bucks) on December 12, 1985\n
	•	8 by Manute Bol, Washington Bullets (vs. Indiana Pacers) on February 26, 1987\n
	•	8 by Dikembe Mutombo, Philadelphia 76ers (at Chicago Bulls) on December 1, 2001\n
	•	8 by Erick Dampier, Golden State Warriors (vs. Los Angeles Clippers) on April 17, 2002\n
	•	Most turnovers in a game\n
	•	14 by John Drew, Atlanta Hawks (at New Jersey Nets) on March 1, 1978\n
	•	14 by Jason Kidd, Phoenix Suns (vs. New York Knicks) on November 17, 2000\n
	•	Quickest disqualification\n
	•	3 minutes by Bubba Wells, Dallas Mavericks (vs. Chicago Bulls) on December 29, 1997\n
    </string>

    <string name="nba_records3">
        Season\n
	•	Most games played\n
	•	88 by Walt Bellamy, 1968–69\n
	•	Most minutes per game average\n
	•	48.52 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most minutes\n
	•	3,882 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Highest points per game average\n
	•	50.36 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most points\n
	•	4,029 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most 50-point games\n
	•	45 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most 40-point games\n
	•	63 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most field goals made\n
	•	1,597 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most field goals attempted\n
	•	3,159 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Most field goals missed\n
	•	1,562 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1961–62\n
	•	Highest field goal percentage\n
	•	72.7% by Wilt Chamberlain, 1972–73\n
	•	Most free throws made\n
	•	840 by Jerry West, 1965–66\n
    </string>

    <string name="nba_records4">
	•	Most 3-point field goals made\n
	•	402 by Stephen Curry, 2015–16\n
	•	Highest 3-point field goals per game average\n
	•	5.1 by Stephen Curry, 2015–16\n
	•	Most 3-point field goals attempted\n
	•	886 by Stephen Curry, 2015–16\n
	•	Highest 3-point field goals attempted per game average\n
	•	11.2 by Stephen Curry, 2015–16\n
	•	Highest 3-point field goal percentage\n
	•	53.6% by Kyle Korver, 2009–10\n
	•	Highest rebounds per game average\n
	•	27.2 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1960–61\n
	•	Most rebounds\n
	•	2,149 by Wilt Chamberlain, 1960–61\n
	•	Highest defensive rebounds per game average\n
	•	13.7 by Elvin Hayes, 1973–74\n
	•	Most defensive rebounds\n
	•	1,111 by Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1975–76\n
	•	Highest offensive rebounds per game average\n
	•	7.2 by Moses Malone, 1978–79\n
	•	Most offensive rebounds\n
	•	587 by Moses Malone, 1978–79\n
	•	Highest assists per game average\n
	•	14.54 by John Stockton, 1989–90\n
    </string>

    <string name="nba_records5">
        Career\n
	•	Most games\n
	•	1,611 by Robert Parish\n
	•	Most consecutive games\n
	•	1,192 by A.C. Green\n
	•	Most minutes per game\n
	•	45.8 by Wilt Chamberlain\n
	•	Most minutes\n
	•	57,446 by Kareem Abdul-Jabbar\n
	•	Highest points per game average\n
	•	30.12 by Michael Jordan\n
	•	Most points\n
	•	38,387 by Kareem Abdul-Jabbar\n
	•	Most seasons leading league in points\n
	•	11 by Michael Jordan\n
	•	Most seasons leading league in points per game\n
	•	10 by Michael Jordan\n
	•	Most consecutive seasons leading league in points\n
	•	7 by Wilt Chamberlain (1959–60–1965–66) and Michael Jordan (1986–87–1992–93)\n
	•	Most 60+ point games\n
	•	32 by Wilt Chamberlain\n
	•	Most 50+ point games\n
	•	118 by Wilt Chamberlain\n
	•	Most 40+ point games\n
	•	271 by Wilt Chamberlain\n
	•	Most 30+ point games\n
	•	562 by Michael Jordan\n
	•	Most 20+ point games\n
	•	1,134 by Karl Malone\n
	•	Most 10+ point games\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records_title1">
        Championships\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records1">
•	Most Super Bowl Wins, 6\n
Pittsburgh Steelers\n
	•	Most Super Bowl Appearances, 8\n
Dallas Cowboys 1970, 1971, 1975, 1977, 1978, 1992, 1993, 1995\n
Pittsburgh Steelers 1974, 1975, 1978, 1979, 1995, 2005, 2008, 2010\n
New England Patriots 1985, 1996, 2001, 2003, 2004, 2007, 2011, 2014\n
Denver Broncos 1977, 1986, 1987, 1989, 1997, 1998, 2013, 2015\n
	•	Most League Championships, 13\n
Green Bay Packers 1929–1931, 1936, 1939, 1944, 1961–62, 1965–67, 1996, 2010\n
	•	Most Conference Championship Game Appearances, 15\n
Pittsburgh Steelers 1972, 1974-76, 1978-79, 1984, 1994-1995, 1997, 2001, 2004-2005, 2008, 2010\n
San Francisco 49ers 1970-1971, 1981, 1983-1984, 1988-1990, 1992-1994, 1997, 2011-2013\n
	•	Most Consecutive League Championships, 3\n
Green Bay Packers 1929–31, 1965–67\n
	•	Most Consecutive Times Finishing First in a Division, Regular Season, 7\n
Los Angeles Rams 1973–79\n
New England Patriots 2009-2015\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records_title2">
        Games Won\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records2">
•	Highest Winning Percentage for Regular Season, .570 (741-555-42)\n
Chicago Bears 1960–2015\n
	•	Highest Winning Percentage for Post Season, .682 (15–7)\n
Baltimore Ravens 2000–2014\n
	•	Most Games Won (regular season only), Franchise History, 741\n
Chicago Bears 1919–2015\n
	•	Most Games Won (including playoffs), Franchise History, 758\n
Chicago Bears 1919–2015\n
	•	Most Games Won (regular season only), since 1970 merger, 433\n
Pittsburgh Steelers: 1970–2015\n
	•	Most Games Won (including playoffs), since 1970 merger, 467\n
Pittsburgh Steelers 1970–2015\n
	•	Most Consecutive Games Won (including playoffs), 21\n
New England Patriots 2003–2004\n
	•	Most Consecutive Games Won (regular season only), 23\n
Indianapolis Colts 2008–2009\n
	•	Most Consecutive Games Without Defeat, 25\n
Canton Bulldogs 1921–1923\n
	•	Most Games Won, Regular Season, 16\n
New England Patriots, 2007\n
	•	Most Consecutive Winning Seasons, Franchise History, 20\n
Dallas Cowboys 1966–1985\n
	•	Most Consecutive Home Games Won, 27\n
Miami Dolphins 1971-1974\n
	•	Most Consecutive Home Games Won (including playoffs), 31\n
Miami Dolphins 1971–1974\n
	•	Most Consecutive Home Games Without Defeat, 30\n
Green Bay Packers 1928–1933\n
	•	Most Consecutive Road Games Won, 18\n
San Francisco 49ers 1988–1990\n
	•	Most Consecutive Road Games Without Defeat, 18\n
San Francisco 49ers 1988–1990\n
	•	Most Shutout Games Won or Tied, Season, 11\n
Pottsville Maroons: 1926\n
	•	Most Consecutive Shutout Games Won or Tied, 13\n
Akron Pros, 1920–1921\n
	•	Most Total Wins Over 2 Consecutive Seasons, 34 (28 Regular Season and 6 Post Season)\n
New England Patriots 2003–2004\n
	•	Most Total Wins Over 3 Consecutive Seasons, 46 (39 Regular Season and 7 Post Season)\n
Denver Broncos 1996–1998\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records_title3">
        Losses\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records3">
•	Lowest All-time Winning Percentage for Regular Season, current franchises, .385 (241–386-1)\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers, 1976–2015\n
	•	Lowest All-time Winning Percentage for Post Season, .263 (5–14)\n
Cincinnati Bengals, 1970–2015\n
	•	Lowest All-time Winning Percentage, combined Regular Season and Post Season, .385 (247–395–1)\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers, 1976–2015\n
	•	Most Consecutive Post Season Losses, 8\n
Detroit Lions, Jan. 12, 1992-ongoing\n
Kansas City Chiefs, Jan. 23, 1994-2016\n
Cincinnati Bengals, 1990-ongoing\n
	•	Longest Losing Streak, Multiple seasons, 26 games\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers: 1976–1977\n
	•	Most Losses, Season / Longest Losing Streak in a Season, 16 games (in 16 games season)\n
Detroit Lions: 2008\n
	•	Most consecutive losing seasons, 14 seasons\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers: 1983–1996\n
	•	Most consecutive seasons without a winning record, 20 seasons\n
New Orleans Saints: 1967–1986\n
	•	Longest Home Game Losing Streak, 14 games\n
Dallas Cowboys: 1988–1989\n
St. Louis Rams: 2008–2010\n
	•	Longest Road Game Losing Streak, 26 games\n
Detroit Lions: 2007–2010\n
	•	Longest Road Streak Without Win (Losses or Ties), 26 games\n
Detroit Lions 2007–2010\n
	•	Most Shutout Losses or Ties in a Season, 8\n
Frankford Yellow Jackets (lost 6, tied 2) 1927\n
Brooklyn Dodgers (lost 8) 1931\n
	•	Most Consecutive Shutout Losses or Ties, 8\n
Rochester Jeffersons (lost 6) 1922–1924\n
    </string>

     <string name="nfl_records_title4">
        Scoring\n
    </string>

    <string name="nfl_records4">
        •	Most Seasons Leading League Scoring, 10\n
Chicago Bears: 1932, 1934–35, 1939, 1941–43, 1946–47, 1956\n
	•	Most Consecutive Seasons Leading League Scoring, 4\n
San Francisco 49ers: 1992–95\n
	•	Most Points, Season, 606\n
Denver Broncos: 2013\n
	•	Most Points at Home, Season, 329\n
New Orleans Saints: 2011\n
	•	Most Points on the Road, Season, 314\n
New England Patriots: 2007\n
	•	Fewest Points at Home, Season, since 1940, 20\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers: 1977, (7 games)\n
	•	Fewest Points on the Road, 8-road game season, since, 1940, 41\n
Cincinnati Bengals: 2000\n
	•	Most Points per Game, Season (Min 10 games), 38.83\n
Los Angeles Rams: 1950 (466 points in 12 games)\n
	•	Most Points per Home Game, Season, 41.1\n
New Orleans Saints: 2011\n
	•	Fewest Points, Season, 37\n
Cincinnati Reds/St. Louis Gunners: 1934\n
	•	Fewest Points, 14 game season, 103\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers: 1977\n
	•	Fewest Points, 16 game season, 140\n
Seattle Seahawks: 1992\n
	•	Games Scoring 50+ Points, Season, 3\n
New York Giants: 1950\n
Los Angeles Rams: 1950\n
San Diego Chargers: 1963 (including a postseason win)\n
Dallas Cowboys: 1966\n
Minnesota Vikings: 1969\n
Denver Broncos: 2013\n
	•	Most Games Scoring 30+ Points, Season, 13\n
Denver Broncos: 2013\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 10+ points, 110\n
Indianapolis Colts, 2003-2009\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 20+ points, 30\n
Denver Broncos, 2012-2014\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 30+ points, 14\n
St. Louis Rams, Nov. 28, 1999-Oct. 29, 2000\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 40+ points, 4\n
Indianapolis Colts, Nov. 14, 2004-Dec. 5, 2004\n
St. Louis Rams, Sept. 17, 2000-Oct. 15, 2000\n
	•	Most Points, Single Team, Game, 73\n
Chicago Bears (73) (vs Washington Redskins (0)), Dec 9, 1940, (Championship Game)\n
	•	Most Points, Single Team, Regular Season Game, 72\n
Washington Redskins (vs New York Giants) Nov 27, 1966\n
	•	Most Points, Single Team, Game, Since AFL/NFL Merger, 62\n
New York Giants (vs Philadelphia Eagles) Nov 26, 1972\n
Atlanta Falcons (vs New Orleans Saints) Sep 16, 1973\n
New York Jets (vs Tampa Bay Buccaneers) Nov 17, 1985\n
Jacksonville Jaguars (vs Miami Dolphins) Jan 15, 2000 (Postseason)\n
New Orleans Saints (vs Indianapolis Colts) Oct 23, 2011\n
	•	Most Points, Both Teams, Game, 113\n
Washington Redskins (72) vs New York Giants (41), Nov 27, 1966\n
	•	Most Points, Both Teams, Game, Since AFL/NFL Merger, 106\n
Cincinnati Bengals (58) vs Cleveland Browns (48), Nov 28, 2004\n
	•	Most Points, Shutout Victory, Game, 73\n
Chicago Bears vs Washington Redskins, Dec 9, 1940 (Championship Game)\n
	•	Most Points, Shutout Victory, Game, Since AFL/NFL Merger, 59\n
Los Angeles Rams vs Atlanta Falcons, Dec 4, 1976\n
New England Patriots vs Tennessee Titans, Oct 18, 2009\n
	•	Fewest Points, Both Teams, Game, 0\n
In many games; last: New York Giants vs Detroit Lions, Nov 7, 1943\n
	•	Fewest Points, Shutout Victory, Game, 2\n
Akron Pros vs Buffalo All-Americans, Nov 29, 1923\n
Kansas City Cowboys vs Buffalo Rangers, Nov 21, 1926\n
Frankford Yellow Jackets vs Green Bay Packers, Nov 29, 1928\n
Green Bay Packers vs Chicago Bears, Oct 16, 1932\n
Chicago Bears vs Green Bay Packers, Sep 18, 1938\n
	•	Fewest Points, Shutout Victory, Game, Since AFL/NFL Merger, 3\n
Minnesota Vikings vs Green Bay Packers, Nov 14, 1971\n
Buffalo Bills vs Atlanta Falcons, Oct 16, 1977\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers vs Kansas City Chiefs, Dec 16, 1979\n
New England Patriots vs Miami Dolphins, Dec 12, 1982\n
New York Jets vs Washington Redskins, Dec 11, 1993\n
Pittsburgh Steelers vs Miami Dolphins, Nov 26, 2007\n
	•	Most Points Overcome to Win Game, 32\n
Buffalo Bills vs Houston Oilers, Jan 3, 1993, (trailed 3–35, won 41–38, OT) (Playoff Game)\n
	•	Most Points Overcome to Win Regular Season Game, 28\n
San Francisco 49ers vs New Orleans Saints, Dec 7, 1980, (OT) (trailed 7–35, won 38–35)\n
	•	Most Points Overcome to Win Game on the Road, 25\n
Cleveland Browns vs Tennessee Titans, Oct 5, 2014, (trailed 3–28, won 29-28)\n
	•	Most Points Overcome to Tie a Game,\n
Denver Broncos vs Buffalo Bills, Nov 27, 1960 (trailed 7–38, tied 38–38)\n
	•	Largest First Quarter Deficit Overcome to Win Game, 21\n
Miami Dolphins vs New England Patriots, Dec 15, 1974 (trailed 0–21, won 34–27)\n
Cincinnati Bengals vs Seattle Seahawks, Sep 6, 1981 (trailed 0–21, won 27–21)\n
Arizona Cardinals vs Philadelphia Eagles, Sep 12, 1999 (trailed 0–21, won 25–24)\n
Washington Redskins vs Carolina Panthers, Oct 3, 1999 (trailed 0–21, won 38–36)\n
Tennessee Titans vs Atlanta Falcons, Nov 23, 2003 (trailed 0–21, won 38–31)\n
Miami Dolphins vs Buffalo Bills, Dec 4, 2005 (trailed 0–21, won 24–23)\n
San Diego Chargers vs Cincinnati Bengals, Nov 12, 2006 (trailed 0–21, won 49–41)\n
New England Patriots vs Buffalo Bills, Jan 1, 2012 (trailed 0–21, won 49–21)\n
	•	Largest Halftime Deficit Overcome to Win Game, 28\n
San Francisco 49ers vs New Orleans Saints, Dec 7, 1980, (OT) (trailed 7–35, won 38–35)\n
	•	Largest Halftime Deficit Overcome to Win Game in Regulation Time, 24\n
Philadelphia Eagles vs Washington Redskins, Oct 27, 1946 (trailed 0–24, won 28–24)\n
Los Angeles Rams vs Tampa Bay Buccaneers, Dec 6, 1992 (trailed 3–27, won 31–27)\n
Denver Broncos vs San Diego Chargers, Oct 15, 2012 (trailed 0–24, won 35–24)\n
	•	Largest Third Quarter Deficit Overcome to Win Game, 25\n
St. Louis Cardinals vs Tampa Bay Buccaneers, Nov 8, 1987 (trailed 3–28, won 31–28)\n
    </string>

    <string name="nfl_records_title5">
        Touchdowns\n
    </string>

    <string name="nfl_records5">
•	Most Touchdowns, season, 76\n
Denver Broncos: 2013\n
	•	Fewest Touchdowns, season, since 1946, 11\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers: 1977\n
	•	Fewest Offensive Touchdowns, season, since 1943, 7\n
Tampa Bay Buccaneers: 1977\n
	•	Most Touchdowns, Single Team, Regular Season, game, 10\n
Washington Redskins (vs. New York Giants), Nov. 27, 1966\n
	•	Most Touchdowns, Both Teams, game, 16\n
Washington Redskins (vs. New York Giants), Nov. 27, 1966\n
	•	Most Touchdowns, Single Team, Post Season, game, 11\n
Chicago Bears (vs. Washington Redskins), Dec. 8, 1940\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 1+ touchdowns, 166\n
Cleveland Browns: 1957-1969\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 2+ touchdowns, 47\n
New England Patriots: September 27, 2009-September 9, 2012\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 3+ touchdowns, 21\n
Miami Dolphins: November 20, 1983-December 17, 1984\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 4+ touchdowns, 12\n
Denver Broncos: Dec. 16, 2012-Nov. 10, 2013\n
New England Patriots: Nov. 14, 2010-Oct. 2, 2011\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 5+ touchdowns, 5\n
4 times, most recently\n
St. Louis Rams: Sept. 17, 2000-Oct. 22, 2000\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 6+ touchdowns (since 1940), 3\n
8 times, most recently\n
New Orleans Saints: Dec. 18, 2011-Jan. 1, 2012\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 7+ touchdowns (since 1940), 3\n
Chicago Bears: Oct. 5, 1941-Oct. 19, 1941\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 8+ touchdowns, 2\n
Los Angeles Rams: Oct. 22, 1950-Oct. 29, 1950\n
	•	Most consecutive games scoring 9+ touchdowns, 2\n
Los Angeles Rams: Oct. 22, 1950-Oct. 29, 1950\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 1+ touchdown, since AFL-NFL Merger, 82\n
New Orleans Saints: Oct. 23, 2005-Nov. 15, 2015\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 1+ touchdown, 85\n
Cleveland Browns: 1956-1969\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 2+ touchdowns, 33\n
New England Patriots: Oct. 11, 2009-Sept. 29, 2013\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 3+ touchdowns, 13\n
Chicago Bears: Sept. 28, 1941-Nov. 14, 1943\n
San Francisco 49ers: Sept. 2, 1984-Oct. 27, 1985\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 4+ touchdowns, 12\n
Cleveland Browns: Nov. 21, 1948-Oct. 7, 1950\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 5+ touchdowns (since 1940), 3\n
15 times, most recently\n
Dallas Cowboys: Dec. 4, 2014-Dec. 28, 2014\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 6+ touchdowns (since 1940), 3\n
Houston Oilers: Nov. 5, 1961-Dec. 17, 1961\n
	•	Most consecutive road games scoring 7+ touchdowns (since 1940), 2\n
Cleveland Browns: Dec. 8, 1946-Sept. 12, 1947\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 1+ touchdowns, 112\n
Cleveland/Los Angeles Rams: Sept. 20, 1942-Oct. 21, 1962\n
Indianapolis Colts: Nov. 2, 1997-Nov. 6, 2011\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 2+ touchdowns, 42\n
Miami Dolphins: Sept. 9, 1982-Dec. 10, 1987\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 3+ touchdowns, 21\n
Miami Dolphins: Oct. 9, 1983-Sept. 14, 1986\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 4+ touchdowns, 12\n
Oakland Raiders: Sept. 24, 2000-Dec. 9, 2001\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 5+ touchdowns, 5\n
5 times, most recently,\n
Green Bay Packers: Nov. 14, 2011-Jan. 1, 2012\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 6+ touchdowns, 4\n
San Francisco 49ers: Sept. 4, 1949-Oct. 16, 1949\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 8+ touchdowns, 2\n
Los Angeles Rams: Oct. 22, 1950-Oct. 29, 1950\n
	•	Most consecutive home games scoring 9+ touchdowns, 2\n
Los Angeles Rams: Oct. 22, 1950-Oct. 29, 1950
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records_title">
        Season records\n
    </string>

    <string name="mlb_records">

Season	Franchise	League	Wins	Losses	Pct.	Finish\n
1906	Chicago Cubs	    NL	116	36	.763	Lost 1906 World Series\n
1902	Pittsburgh Pirates	NL	103	36	.741	National League Champions\n
1886	Chicago White Stockings	NL	90	34	.726	Lost 1886 World Series\n
1909	Pittsburgh Pirates	NL	110	42	.724	Won 1909 World Series\n
1954	Cleveland Indians	AL	111	43	.721	Lost 1954 World Series\n
2001	Seattle Mariners	AL	116	46	.716	Lost 2001 ALCS\n
1927	New York Yankees	AL	110	44	.714	Won 1927 World Series\n
1886	Detroit Wolverines	NL	87	36	.707	2nd place in National League\n
1897	Boston Beaneaters	NL	93	39	.705	Lost 1897 Temple Cup\n
1998	New York Yankees	AL	114	48	.704	Won 1998 World Series\n
1907	Chicago Cubs	NL	107	45	.704	Won 1907 World Series\n
1931	Philadelphia Athletics	AL	107	45	.704	Lost 1931 World Series\n
1887	St. Louis Browns	AA	95	40	.704	Lost 1887 World Series\n
1939	New York Yankees	AL	106	45	.702	Won 1939 World Series\n
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records_title1">
       Hitting records: single game\n
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records1">
Most hits in a nine-inning game: 7 by Wilbert Robinson, June 10, 1892, and Rennie Stennett, September 16, 1975.\n
Most hits in an extra-inning game: 9, Johnny Burnett, July 10, 1932.\n
Most total bases in a nine-inning game: 19 (4 home runs, a double and a single), Shawn Green, May 23, 2002.\n
    </string>

    <string name="mlb_records_title2">
       Pitching records: single game\n
    </string>

    <string name="mlb_records2">
Most home runs allowed: 7, Charlie Sweeney, June 12, 1886\n
Most strikeouts: 21, Tom Cheney, September 12, 1962 (16 innings)\n
Most strikeouts in a nine-inning game: 20 by Kerry Wood and Roger Clemens (twice)\n
Most consecutive home runs allowed: 4 by Paul Foytack, July 31, 1963, Chase Wright, April 22, 2007, and Dave Bush, August 11, 2010\n
Oldest pitcher to win a game: Age 49, Jamie Moyer, May 16, 2012\n
    </string>

    <string name="mlb_records_title3">
      Catcher records: career\n
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records3">
Most runners caught stealing: 810, Gary Carter\n
Most stolen bases allowed: 1,498, Gary Carter\n
Most stolen-base attempts: 2,308, Gary Carter\n
Highest caught-stealing : 57.40, Roy Campanella\n
Most pick-offs: 81, Ivan Rodriguez\n
Most no-hitters caught: 4, Jason Varitek\n
    </string>

    <string name="mlb_records_title4">
     Catcher records: single season\n
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records4">
Most runners caught stealing: Jody Davis, 89 (1986)\n
Most stolen bases allowed: Mike Piazza, 155 (1996)\n
Highest caught-stealing : Mike LaValliere, 72.73 (1993)\n
Most no-hitters caught: 2, Carlos Ruiz (2010) (List of Major League Baseball no-hitters)\n
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records_title5">
     Batting records: career\n
    </string>

     <string name="mlb_records5">
Highest batting average	Ty Cobb	.366\n
Most singles	Pete Rose	3,215\n
Most doubles	Tris Speaker	792\n
Most triples	Sam Crawford	309\n
Most home runs	Barry Bonds	762\n
Most grand slams	Alex Rodriguez\n
Most home runs by a pitcher	Wes Ferrell	38\n
Most grand slams by a pitcher	Madison Bumgarner	2\n
Most RBI	Hank Aaron	2,297\n
Most hits	Pete Rose	4,256\n
Most runs scored	Rickey Henderson	2,295\n
Highest on-base percentage	Ted Williams	.482\n
Most stolen bases	Rickey Henderson	1,406\n
Most steals of home	Ty Cobb	54\n
Highest slugging percentage	Babe Ruth	.690\n
Highest OPS	Babe Ruth	1.164\n
Most walks	Barry Bonds	2,558\n
Most intentional walks	Barry Bonds	688\n
Most strikeouts	Reggie Jackson	2,597\n
Most at-bats	Pete Rose	14,053\n
Most total bases	Hank Aaron	6,856\n
Most runs created	Barry Bonds	2,892\n
Most games played	Pete Rose	3,562\n
    </string>

     <string name="nhl_records_title">
    Team Records\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records_title1">
     Season records\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records">
Most Points in 70 or More Games: 132, by the 1976–77 Montreal Canadiens\n
Most Points in 44–60 Games: 83, by the 1943–44 Montreal Canadiens\n
Most Points in 36 or Fewer Games: 52, by the 1925–26 Ottawa Senators\n
Fewest Points in 70 or More Games: 21, by the 1974–75 Washington Capitals\n
Fewest Points in 44–60 Games: 12, by the 1930–31 Philadelphia Quakers\n
Fewest Points in 36 or Fewer Games: 8, by the 1919–20 Quebec Bulldogs\n
Most Wins in 70 or More Games: 62, by the 1995–96 Detroit Red Wings\n
Most Wins in 44–60 Games: 38, by the 1943–44 Montreal Canadiens and 1944–45 Montreal Canadiens\n
Most Wins in 36 or Fewer Games: 24, by the 1925–26 Ottawa Senators\n
Fewest Wins in 70 or More Games: 8, by the 1974–75 Washington Capitals\n
Fewest Wins in 44–60 Games: 4, by the 1930–31 Philadelphia Quakers\n
Fewest Wins in 36 or Fewer Games: 4, by the 1919–20 Quebec Bulldogs\n
Most Ties in 70 or More Games: 24, by the 1969–70 Philadelphia Flyers\n
Most Ties in 44–60 Games: 15, by the 1928–29 Montreal Canadiens and 1942–43 Chicago Blackhawks\n
Most Ties in 36 or Fewer Games: 5, by 1925–26 Montreal Maroons\n
Fewest Ties in 70 or More Games: 2, by the 1992–93 San Jose Sharks\n
Fewest Ties in 44–60 Games: 1, by the 1929–30 Boston Bruins\n
Most Shootout Wins: 15, by the 2007–08 Edmonton Oilers\n
Most Shootout Losses: 13, by the 2013–14 New Jersey Devils\n
Most Losses in 70 or More Games: 71, by the 1992–93 San Jose Sharks\n
Most Losses in 44–60 Games: 39, by 1943–44 New York Rangers\n
Most Losses in 36 or Fewer Games: 24, by the 1924–25 Boston Bruins\n
Fewest Losses in 70 or More Games: 8, by the 1976–77 Montreal Canadiens\n
Fewest Losses in 44–60 Games: 5, by the 1943–44 Montreal Canadiens and 1929–30 Boston Bruins\n
Fewest Losses in 36 or Fewer Games: 5 by the 1919–20 Ottawa Senators\n
Most Goals in 70 or More Games: 446, by the 1983–84 Edmonton Oilers\n
Most Goals in 44–60 Games: 234, by the 1943–44 Montreal Canadiens\n
Most Goals in 36 or Fewer Games: 129, by the 1919–20 Montreal Canadiens\n
Fewest Goals in 70 or More Games: 133, by the 1953–54 Chicago Blackhawks\n
Fewest Goals in 44–60 Games: 33, by the 1928–29 Chicago Blackhawks\n
Fewest Goals in 36 or Fewer Games: 45, by the 1924–25 Montreal Canadiens\n
Most Goals Against in 70 or More Games: 446, by the 1974–75 Washington Capitals\n
Most Goals Against in 44–60 Games: 310, by the 1943–44 New York Rangers\n
Most Goals Against in 36 or Fewer Games: 177, by the 1919–20 Quebec Bulldogs\n
Fewest Goals Against in 70 or More Games: 131, by the 1953–54 Toronto Maple Leafs and 1955–56 Montreal Canadiens\n
Fewest Goals Against in 44–60 Games: 43 by the 1928–29 Montreal Canadiens\n
Fewest Goals Against in 36 or Fewer Games: 42, by the 1925–26 Ottawa Senators\n
Greatest Goal Differential: +216, by the 1976–77 Montreal Canadiens\n
Lowest Goal Differential: -265, by the 1974–75 Washington Capitals\n
Best Power Play Percentage in a Season: 31.88 percent, by the 1977–78 Montreal Canadiens\n
Worst Power Play Percentage in a Season: 9.35 percent, by the 1997–98 Tampa Bay Lightning\n
Best Penalty Kill Percentage in a Season: 89.58 percent, by the 2011–12 New Jersey Devils\n
Worst Penalty Kill Percentage in a Season: 67.70 percent, by the 1979–80 Los Angeles Kings\n
Best Home Record: 36–2–2 by the 1975–76 Philadelphia Flyers\n
Worst Home Record: 7–28–5 by the 1974–75 Washington Capitals\n
Best Away Record: 31–7–3 by the 2005–06 Detroit Red Wings\n
Worst Away Record: 1–41–0, by the 1992–93 Ottawa Senators\n
Most Shutout Wins in a Season: 22 of 44 games played (50.0 percent), by the 1928–29 Montreal Canadiens\n
Most Shutout Losses in a Season: 20 of 44 games played (45.5 percent), by the 1928–29 Chicago Blackhawks\n
    </string>

 <string name="nhl_records_title2">
     Individual records\n
    </string>

     <string name="nhl_records_title3">
     Seasons\n
    </string>

 <string name="nhl_records2">
Most seasons: Gordie Howe, (1946–47 to 1970–1971; 1979–1980), Chris Chelios, (1983–84 to 2009–10, except for the 2004–05 NHL lockout), 26\n
Most playoff seasons: Chris Chelios, 24 (1983–84 to 2008–09, except for 1997–98 and the 2004–05 NHL lockout year)\n
Most consecutive playoff seasons: Larry Robinson, (1972–73 to 1991–92), Nicklas Lidstrom, (1991–92 to 2011–12, except for the 2004–05 NHL lockout), 20\n
    </string>

     <string name="nhl_records_title4">
     Games\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records3">
Most games: Gordie Howe, 1,767\n
Most games, including playoffs: Mark Messier, 1,992\n
Most playoff games: Chris Chelios 266\n
Most games played in a single NHL season, not including playoffs: Jimmy Carson (1992–93) and Bob Kudelski (1993–94), 86\n
Most consecutive games: Doug Jarvis, 964 (October 8, 1975 – October 10, 1987)\n
Most consecutive games by a defenceman: Jay Bouwmeester, 737\n
Oldest player to play a game: Gordie Howe, 52 years, 11 days\n
Most games by a coach in the Stanley Cup Final: Dick Irvin (Chicago(5), Toronto(29), Montreal(43), 77\n
Most games played in the Finals: Red Kelly (Detroit(37), Toronto(28), Henri Richard (Montreal), 65\n
Most games won by a coach in the Stanley Cup Finals: Scotty Bowman, 36 (Montreal(20), Pittsburgh(4), Detroit(12)\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records_title5">
     Stanley Cups\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records4">
Most Stanley Cups, as a player: Henri Richard, Montreal Canadiens, 11 (1956, 57, 58, 59, 60, 65, 66, 68, 69, 71, 73)\n
Most Stanley Cups, as a non-player: Scotty Bowman, 14 - Montreal (1973, 76, 77, 78,79), Pittsburgh (1991, 92), Detroit (1997, 98, 2002, 08), Chicago (2010, 13, 15)\n
Most Stanley Cups, combined player or non-player: Jean Beliveau, Montreal Canadiens, 17 Player - (1956, 57, 58, 59, 60, 65, 66, 68, 69, 71), Executive - (1973, 76, 77, 78, 79, 86, 93)\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records_title6">
     Goals\n
    </string>

      <string name="nhl_records5">
Most goals career: Wayne Gretzky, 894\n
Most goals playoffs career; Wayne Gretzky, 122\n
Most goals career, including playoffs: Wayne Gretzky, 1,016\n
Most goals, one season: Wayne Gretzky, 92 (1981–82)\n
Most goals, in playoffs one season: Reggie Leach (1976) and Jari Kurri (1985), 19\n
Most goals, one season, including playoffs: Wayne Gretzky, 100 (1983–84)\n
Most goals, one playoff series: Jari Kurri (6 game series), 12 (1985)\n
Most goals in a Stanley Cup Final: Cyclone Taylor (1918, 5 games), Frank Foyston (1919, 5 games), Babe Dye (1922, 5 games), 9\n
Most goals in the Finals, career: Maurice Richard, 34\n
Most goals, 50 games from start of season: Wayne Gretzky, 61 (1981–82 and 1983–84)\n
Fastest 50 goals from start of season: Wayne Gretzky, 39 games (Dec. 30, 1981)\n
Most goals, one game: Joe Malone, 7 (Jan. 31, 1920)\n
Most goals, one regular season game: Joe Malone, 7 (Jan. 31, 1920)\n
Most goals, one regular season home game: Joe Malone, 7 (Jan. 31, 1920)\n
Most goals, one regular season road game: Red Berenson, 6 (Nov. 7, 1968)\n
Most goals, one playoff game: Newsy Lalonde (Mar. 1, 1919), Maurice Richard (Mar. 23, 1944), Darryl Sittler (Apr. 22, 1976), Reggie Leach (May 6, 1976), Mario Lemieux (Apr. 25, 1989), 5\n
Most goals, one home playoff game: Maurice Richard (Mar. 23, 1944), Darryl Sittler (Apr. 22, 1976), Reggie Leach (May 6, 1976), Mario Lemieux (Apr. 25, 1989), 5\n
Most goals, one road playoff game: Newsy Lalonde (Mar. 1, 1919), 5\n
Most goals, one period: Max Bentley (Jan. 28, 1943), Busher Jackson (Nov. 20, 1934), Clint Smith (Mar. 4, 1945), Red Berenson (Nov. 7, 1968), Wayne Gretzky (Feb. 18, 1981), Grant Mulvey (Feb. 3, 1982), Bryan Trottier (Feb. 13, 1982), Johan Franzen (May 6, 2010), Tim Kerr (Apr. 13, 1985), Al Secord (Jan. 7, 1987), Joe Nieuwendyk (Jan. 11, 1989), Peter Bondra (Feb. 5, 1994), Mario Lemieux (Jan. 26, 1997), 4\n
Most goals in one period during the finals: Busher Jackson (Apr. 5, 1932), Ted Lindsay (Apr. 5, 1955), Maurice Richard (Apr. 6, 1957), Wayne Gretzky (May 25, 1985), Dirk Graham (June 1, 1992), Peter Forsberg (June 6, 1996), 3\n
Most game-winning goals in a season: Phil Esposito (1970–71 and 1971–72) and Michel Goulet (1983–84), 16\n
Most game-winning goals in playoffs one season: Brad Richards (2004), 7\n
Most game-winning goals in a playoff series: Mike Bossy (6 game series) (1983), 4\n
Most game-winning goals career: Jaromir Jagr, 124\n
Most game-winning goals playoffs career: Wayne Gretzky, Brett Hull, 24\n
    </string>

    <string name="nhl_records_title7">
    Assists\n
    </string>

    <string name="nhl_records6">
Most assists regular season career: Wayne Gretzky, 1,963\n
Most assists playoffs career: Wayne Gretzky 260\n
Most assists career, including playoffs: Wayne Gretzky, 2,223\n
Most assists, one season: Wayne Gretzky, 163 (1985–86)\n
Most assists, one playoff season: Wayne Gretzky, 31 (1987–88)\n
Most assists, one season, including playoffs: Wayne Gretzky, 174 (1985–86)\n
Most assists, playoff series: Rick Middleton (7 game series) (1983), Wayne Gretzky (6 game series) (1985) 14\n
Most assists, one game: Billy Taylor (Mar. 16, 1947), Wayne Gretzky (Feb. 15, 1980, Dec. 11, 1985, and Feb. 14, 1986), 7\n
Most assists, one road game: Billy Taylor (Mar. 16, 1947), Wayne Gretzky (Dec. 11, 1985), 7\n
Most assists, one playoff game: Mikko Leinonen (Apr. 8, 1982), Wayne Gretzky (Apr. 9, 1987), 6\n
Most assists, one period: Dale Hawerchuk, 5 (Mar. 6, 1984)\n
    </string>

    <string name="nhl_records_title8">
    Points\n
    </string>

    <string name="nhl_records7">
Most points regular season career: Wayne Gretzky, 2,857\n
Most points playoff career: Wayne Gretzky, 382\n
Most points career, including playoffs: Wayne Gretzky, 3,239\n
Most points, one season: Wayne Gretzky, 215 (1985–86)\n
Fastest 100 points from the start of a season: Wayne Gretzky, 34 games (Dec. 27, 1981)\n
Most points, one season, including playoffs: Wayne Gretzky, 255 (1984–85)\n
Most points, one game: Darryl Sittler, 10 (Feb. 7, 1976)\n
Most points, one playoff game: Patrik Sundstrom (Apr. 22, 1988) and Mario Lemieux (Apr. 25, 1989), 8\n
Most points, one road game: Peter Stastny and Anton Stastny,(Feb. 22, 1981), 8\n
Most points, one period: Bryan Trottier, 6 (December 23, 1978, second period)\n
Most points, one playoff season: Wayne Gretzky, 47 (1985)\n
Most points, one playoff series: Rick Middleton (7 game series), 19 (1983)\n
Most points in the Final, one series: Wayne Gretzky, 13 (1988)\n
Most points in the Final, career: Jean Beliveau, 62
    </string>

</resources>
