<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SportsNewsHistoryRecords</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="serie_a_history1">
        Serie A, also called Serie A TIM due to sponsorship by TIM, is a professional league competition for football clubs located at the top of the Italian football league system and has been operating for over eighty years since the 1929–30 season. It had been organized by Lega Calcio until 2010, but a new league, the Lega Serie A, was created for the 2010–11 season. Serie A is regarded as one of the best football leagues in the world and it is often depicted as the most tactical national league. Serie A is the world\'s second-strongest national league according to IFFHS and has produced the highest number of European Cup finalists: Italian clubs have reached the final of the competition on a record 26 different occasions, winning the title 12 times. Serie A is ranked fourth among European leagues according to UEFA\'s league coefficient, behind La Liga, Bundesliga and Premier League, which is based on the performance of Italian clubs in the Champions League and the Europa League during the last five years. Serie A led the UEFA ranking from 1986 to 1988 and from 1990 to 1999.\n
    </string>

     <string name="serie_a_history2">
         In its current format, the Italian Football Championship was revised from having regional and interregional rounds, to a single-tier league from the 1929–30 season onwards. The championship titles won prior to 1929 are officially recognised by FIGC with the same weighting as titles that were subsequently awarded. However, the 1945–46 season, when the league was played over two geographical groups due to the ravages of WWII, is not statistically considered, even if its title is fully official. All the winning teams are recognised with the title of Champion of Italy, which is ratified by the Lega Serie A before the start of the next edition of the championship.\n
    </string>

     <string name="serie_a_history3">
The league hosts three of the world\'s most famous clubs as Juventus, Milan and Internazionale, all founding members of the G-14, a group which represented the largest and most prestigious European football clubs; Serie A was the only league to produce three founding members. More players have won the coveted Ballon d\'Or award while playing at a Serie A club than any other league in the world. - ahead of Spain\'s La Liga, although the actual number of Ballon d\'Or won by players in these two leagues is equal at 18 each if including the FIFA Ballon d\'Or. Milan is the second club with the most official international titles in the world, with 18. Juventus, Italy\'s most successful club of the 20th century and the most successful Italian team, is tied for fourth in Europe and eighth in the world in the same ranking. The club is the only one in the world to have won all possible official continental competitions and the world title. Internazionale, following their achievements in the 2009–10 season, became the first Italian team to have achieved a treble. Juventus, Milan and Inter, along with Roma, Fiorentina, Lazio and Napoli, are known as the Seven Sisters of Italian football.\n
     </string>
    <string name="serie_a_history4">
For most of Serie A\'s history, there were 16 or 18 clubs competing at the top level. Since 2004–05, however, there have been 20 clubs altogether. One season (1947–48) was played with 21 teams for political reasons. Below is a complete record of how many teams played in each season throughout the league\'s history;\n
•	18 clubs: 1929–1934\n
•	16 clubs: 1934–1942\n
•	18 clubs: 1942–1946\n
•	20 clubs: 1946–1947\n
•	21 clubs: 1947–1948\n
•	20 clubs: 1948–1952\n
•	18 clubs: 1952–1967\n
•	16 clubs: 1967–1988\n
•	18 clubs: 1988–2004\n
•	20 clubs: 2004–present
    </string>

    <string name="team_recors_title">
                Team records\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_recors_team">
Most championships won\n
Overall\n
•	32, Juventus\n
        \n
Consecutives\n
•	5, Juventus (1930–31 season to 1934–35 season and from 2011–12 season to 2015–16 season)\n
•	5, Torino (1942–43 season and the 1945–46 season to 1948–49 season)\n
•	5, Internazionale (2005–06 season to 2009–10 season)\n
        \n
Most seasons in Serie A\n
•	84, Internazionale\n
         \n
Most seasons in Serie B\n
•	57, Brescia\n
        \n
Most points in a season\n
2 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1928–29\n
•	4, Bologna\n
6 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1926–27\n
•	14, Torino\n
8 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1927–28 - 1945–46\n
•	22, Torino 1945–46\n
16 Teams (2 points per win) 1934–35 to 1942–43 - 1967–68 to 1987–88\n
•	51, Juventus 1976–77\n
18 Teams (2 points per win) 1929–30 to 1933–34 - 1952–53 to 1966–67 - 1988–89 to 1993–94\n
•	58, Internazionale 1988–89\n
18 Teams (3 points per win) 1994–95 to 2003–04\n
•	82, Milan 2003–04\n
20 Teams (2 points per win) 1946–47 - 1948–49 to 1951–52\n
•	63, Torino 1946–47\n
20 Teams (3 points per win) 2004–05 to present\n
•	102, Juventus 2013–14\n
21 Teams (2 points per win) 1947–48\n
•	65, Torino\n
         \n
Most consecutive wins\n
•	17, Internazionale, 2006–07\n
•	15, Juventus, 2015–16\n
•	13, Juventus, 2013–14 to 2014–15\n
•	12, Juventus, 2013–14\n
•	11, Roma, 2005–06 and 2012–13 to 2013–14\n
•	10, Juventus, 2015-16\n
•	10, Juventus, 1931–32\n
•	10, Milan, 1950–51 and 1989–90\n
•	10, Bologna, 1963–64\n
        \n
Most consecutive home wins\n
•	25, Juventus, 2013–14 to 2014–15\n
        \n
Longest win streaks from the start of a Serie A season\n
•	10, Roma, 2013–14\n
        \n
Longest win streaks without conceding from the start of a Serie A season\n
•	5, Juventus, 2014–15\n
        \n
Most wins in season\n
•	33, Juventus, 2013–14 (38 matches)\n
•	30, Internazionale, 2006–07 (38 matches)\n
•	29, Torino, 1947–48 (40 matches)\n
•	28, Juventus, 2015–16 (38 matches)\n
•	28, Milan, 2005–06 (38 matches)\n
•	27, Internazionale, 1950–51 (38 matches)\n
        \n
Most home wins in season\n
•	19, Juventus, 2013–14 (19 matches)\n
        \n
Most matches won\n
•	1495, Juventus\n
        \n
Most goals scored\n
•	4577, Juventus\n
        \n
Longest unbeaten streaks\n
•	58, Milan, 1990–91 to 1992–93 (26 May 1991, 0–0 v Parma; 21 March 1993, 0–1 v Parma)\n
•	49, Juventus, 2010–11 to 2012–13 (22 May 2011, 2–2 v Napoli; 3 November 2012, 1–3 v Internazionale)\n
        \n
Longest unbeaten streaks in a single Serie A season\n
16 Teams\n
•	30, Perugia, 1978–79\n
18 Teams\n
•	34, Milan, 1991–92\n
20 Teams\n
•	38, Juventus, 2011–12
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="individual_records_title">
                Individual records\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_individual_records">
Most championships won\n
8 Championships\n
•	Virginio Rosetta (2 with Pro Vercelli + 6 with Juventus)\n
•	Giovanni Ferrari (5 with Juventus + 2 with Inter + 1 with Bologna)\n
•	Giuseppe Furino (all with Juventus)\n
        \n
7 Championships\n
•	Roberto Bettega (all with Juventus)\n
•	Alessandro Costacurta (all with Milan)\n
•	Ciro Ferrara (2 with Napoli + 5 with Juventus)\n
•	Paolo Maldini (all with Milan)\n
•	Gaetano Scirea (all with Juventus)\n
•	Guglielmo Gabetto (2 with Juventus + 5 with Torino)\n
•	Gianluigi Buffon (all with Juventus)\n

    </string>

    <string name="top_scorers_title">
        Top Scorers\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_scorers">
1.	Italy	Silvio Piola,	years: 1929–1954 years	274 goals\n
2.	Italy	Francesco Totti,	years: 1992–present 248 goals\n
3.	Sweden	Gunnar Nordahl,	years: 1948–1958	225 goals\n
4.	Italy	Giuseppe Meazza,	years: 1929–1947	216 goals\n
5.  Italy	José Altafini,	years: 1958–1976	216 goals\n
6.	Italy	Antonio Di Natale,	years: 2002–present	208 goals\n
7.	Italy	Roberto Baggio,	years: 1985–2004	205 goals\n
8.	Sweden	Kurt Hamrin,	    years: 1956–1971	190 goals\n
9.	Italy	Giuseppe Signori, years: 1991–2004	188 goals\n
10. Italy	Alessandro Del Piero,	years: 1993–2012	188 goals
    </string>

</resources>
