<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SportsNewsHistoryRecords</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="serie_a_history1">
        Serie A, also called Serie A TIM due to sponsorship by TIM, is a professional league competition for football clubs located at the top of the Italian football league system and has been operating for over eighty years since the 1929–30 season. It had been organized by Lega Calcio until 2010, but a new league, the Lega Serie A, was created for the 2010–11 season. Serie A is regarded as one of the best football leagues in the world and it is often depicted as the most tactical national league. Serie A is the world\'s second-strongest national league according to IFFHS and has produced the highest number of European Cup finalists: Italian clubs have reached the final of the competition on a record 26 different occasions, winning the title 12 times. Serie A is ranked fourth among European leagues according to UEFA\'s league coefficient, behind La Liga, Bundesliga and Premier League, which is based on the performance of Italian clubs in the Champions League and the Europa League during the last five years. Serie A led the UEFA ranking from 1986 to 1988 and from 1990 to 1999.\n
    </string>

     <string name="serie_a_history2">
         In its current format, the Italian Football Championship was revised from having regional and interregional rounds, to a single-tier league from the 1929–30 season onwards. The championship titles won prior to 1929 are officially recognised by FIGC with the same weighting as titles that were subsequently awarded. However, the 1945–46 season, when the league was played over two geographical groups due to the ravages of WWII, is not statistically considered, even if its title is fully official. All the winning teams are recognised with the title of Champion of Italy, which is ratified by the Lega Serie A before the start of the next edition of the championship.\n
    </string>

     <string name="serie_a_history3">
The league hosts three of the world\'s most famous clubs as Juventus, Milan and Internazionale, all founding members of the G-14, a group which represented the largest and most prestigious European football clubs; Serie A was the only league to produce three founding members. More players have won the coveted Ballon d\'Or award while playing at a Serie A club than any other league in the world. - ahead of Spain\'s La Liga, although the actual number of Ballon d\'Or won by players in these two leagues is equal at 18 each if including the FIFA Ballon d\'Or. Milan is the second club with the most official international titles in the world, with 18. Juventus, Italy\'s most successful club of the 20th century and the most successful Italian team, is tied for fourth in Europe and eighth in the world in the same ranking. The club is the only one in the world to have won all possible official continental competitions and the world title. Internazionale, following their achievements in the 2009–10 season, became the first Italian team to have achieved a treble. Juventus, Milan and Inter, along with Roma, Fiorentina, Lazio and Napoli, are known as the Seven Sisters of Italian football.\n
     </string>
    <string name="serie_a_history4">
For most of Serie A\'s history, there were 16 or 18 clubs competing at the top level. Since 2004–05, however, there have been 20 clubs altogether. One season (1947–48) was played with 21 teams for political reasons. Below is a complete record of how many teams played in each season throughout the league\'s history;\n
•	18 clubs: 1929–1934\n
•	16 clubs: 1934–1942\n
•	18 clubs: 1942–1946\n
•	20 clubs: 1946–1947\n
•	21 clubs: 1947–1948\n
•	20 clubs: 1948–1952\n
•	18 clubs: 1952–1967\n
•	16 clubs: 1967–1988\n
•	18 clubs: 1988–2004\n
•	20 clubs: 2004–present
    </string>

    <string name="team_recors_title">
                Team records\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_recors_team">
Most championships won\n
Overall\n
•	32, Juventus\n
        \n
Consecutives\n
•	5, Juventus (1930–31 season to 1934–35 season and from 2011–12 season to 2015–16 season)\n
•	5, Torino (1942–43 season and the 1945–46 season to 1948–49 season)\n
•	5, Internazionale (2005–06 season to 2009–10 season)\n
        \n
Most seasons in Serie A\n
•	84, Internazionale\n
         \n
Most seasons in Serie B\n
•	57, Brescia\n
        \n
Most points in a season\n
2 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1928–29\n
•	4, Bologna\n
6 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1926–27\n
•	14, Torino\n
8 Teams in Final Round (2 points per win) 1927–28 - 1945–46\n
•	22, Torino 1945–46\n
16 Teams (2 points per win) 1934–35 to 1942–43 - 1967–68 to 1987–88\n
•	51, Juventus 1976–77\n
18 Teams (2 points per win) 1929–30 to 1933–34 - 1952–53 to 1966–67 - 1988–89 to 1993–94\n
•	58, Internazionale 1988–89\n
18 Teams (3 points per win) 1994–95 to 2003–04\n
•	82, Milan 2003–04\n
20 Teams (2 points per win) 1946–47 - 1948–49 to 1951–52\n
•	63, Torino 1946–47\n
20 Teams (3 points per win) 2004–05 to present\n
•	102, Juventus 2013–14\n
21 Teams (2 points per win) 1947–48\n
•	65, Torino\n
         \n
Most consecutive wins\n
•	17, Internazionale, 2006–07\n
•	15, Juventus, 2015–16\n
•	13, Juventus, 2013–14 to 2014–15\n
•	12, Juventus, 2013–14\n
•	11, Roma, 2005–06 and 2012–13 to 2013–14\n
•	10, Juventus, 2015-16\n
•	10, Juventus, 1931–32\n
•	10, Milan, 1950–51 and 1989–90\n
•	10, Bologna, 1963–64\n
        \n
Most consecutive home wins\n
•	25, Juventus, 2013–14 to 2014–15\n
        \n
Longest win streaks from the start of a Serie A season\n
•	10, Roma, 2013–14\n
        \n
Longest win streaks without conceding from the start of a Serie A season\n
•	5, Juventus, 2014–15\n
        \n
Most wins in season\n
•	33, Juventus, 2013–14 (38 matches)\n
•	30, Internazionale, 2006–07 (38 matches)\n
•	29, Torino, 1947–48 (40 matches)\n
•	28, Juventus, 2015–16 (38 matches)\n
•	28, Milan, 2005–06 (38 matches)\n
•	27, Internazionale, 1950–51 (38 matches)\n
        \n
Most home wins in season\n
•	19, Juventus, 2013–14 (19 matches)\n
        \n
Most matches won\n
•	1495, Juventus\n
        \n
Most goals scored\n
•	4577, Juventus\n
        \n
Longest unbeaten streaks\n
•	58, Milan, 1990–91 to 1992–93 (26 May 1991, 0–0 v Parma; 21 March 1993, 0–1 v Parma)\n
•	49, Juventus, 2010–11 to 2012–13 (22 May 2011, 2–2 v Napoli; 3 November 2012, 1–3 v Internazionale)\n
        \n
Longest unbeaten streaks in a single Serie A season\n
16 Teams\n
•	30, Perugia, 1978–79\n
18 Teams\n
•	34, Milan, 1991–92\n
20 Teams\n
•	38, Juventus, 2011–12
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="individual_records_title">
                Individual records\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_individual_records">
Most championships won\n
8 Championships\n
•	Virginio Rosetta (2 with Pro Vercelli + 6 with Juventus)\n
•	Giovanni Ferrari (5 with Juventus + 2 with Inter + 1 with Bologna)\n
•	Giuseppe Furino (all with Juventus)\n
        \n
7 Championships\n
•	Roberto Bettega (all with Juventus)\n
•	Alessandro Costacurta (all with Milan)\n
•	Ciro Ferrara (2 with Napoli + 5 with Juventus)\n
•	Paolo Maldini (all with Milan)\n
•	Gaetano Scirea (all with Juventus)\n
•	Guglielmo Gabetto (2 with Juventus + 5 with Torino)\n
•	Gianluigi Buffon (all with Juventus)\n

    </string>

    <string name="top_scorers_title">
        Top Scorers\n
    </string>

    <string name="serie_a_scorers">
1.	Italy	Silvio Piola,	years: 1929–1954 274 goals\n
2.	Italy	Francesco Totti,	years: 1992–present 248 goals\n
3.	Sweden	Gunnar Nordahl,	years: 1948–1958	225 goals\n
4.	Italy	Giuseppe Meazza,	years: 1929–1947	216 goals\n
5.  Italy	José Altafini,	years: 1958–1976	216 goals\n
6.	Italy	Antonio Di Natale,	years: 2002–present	208 goals\n
7.	Italy	Roberto Baggio,	years: 1985–2004	205 goals\n
8.	Sweden	Kurt Hamrin,	    years: 1956–1971	190 goals\n
9.	Italy	Giuseppe Signori, years: 1991–2004	188 goals\n
10. Italy	Alessandro Del Piero,	years: 1993–2012	188 goals
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_history">
        The Primera Division (First Division) of the Liga de Futbol Profesional (LFP), commonly known in English as La Liga, is the top professional association football division of the Spanish football league system. It is officially named Liga BBVA (BBVA League) for sponsorship reasons. It is contested by 20 teams, with the three lowest-placed teams relegated to the Segunda Division and replaced by the top two teams in that division plus the winner of a playoff.\n
A total of 60 teams have competed in La Liga since its inception. Nine teams have been crowned champions, with Real Madrid winning the title a record 32 times and Barcelona 23 times. Real Madrid dominated the championship from the 1950s through the 1980s. Since the 1990s, however, Real Madrid and Barcelona have both dominated, although La Liga has seen other champions, including Atletico Madrid, Valencia, and Deportivo de La Coruna. In more recent years, Atletico Madrid has joined a coalition of now three teams dominating La Liga alongside Real Madrid and Barcelona.\n
La Liga has been the top league in Europe over the last five years, according to UEFA league coefficient and La Liga clubs have been the top rated club in Europe more times than any other league (18) double that of second placed Serie A with (9). La Liga based clubs have also won the most IFFS World\'s Club Team of the Year awards (9). La Liga clubs have won the most UEFA Champions League tournaments (15) and Real Madrid are the competition\'s most successful club, with ten titles.\n
        La Liga clubs have also won the highest number of UEFA Cup,UEFA Europa League titles and Sevilla are the most successful club in the competition\'s history with 4 titles. La Liga is the first and only league to be represented by both finalists in a UEFA Champions League final on two occasions.\n
        La Liga-based players have won the highest number of FIFA World Player of the Year awards (11), Ballon d\'Or awards (19) and UEFA Best Player in Europe awards (4).\n
        La Liga players also represent the most FIFPro World XI and UEFA Team of the Year places. Real Madrid and Barcelona are the La Liga clubs to have won the UEFA Champions League.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_foundation_title">
        Foundation\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_foundation">
In April 1927, José María Acha, a director at Arenas Club de Getxo, first proposed the idea of a national league in Spain. After much debate about the size of the league and who would take part, the Real Federación Española de Fútbol eventually agreed on the ten teams who would form the first Primera División in 1929. Barcelona, Real Madrid, Athletic Bilbao, Real Sociedad, Arenas Club de Getxo and Real Unión were all selected as previous winners of the Copa del Rey. Atlético Madrid, Espanyol and Europa qualified as Copa del Rey runners-up and Racing de Santander qualified through a knockout competition. Only three of the founding clubs, Real Madrid, Barcelona and Athletic Bilbao, have never been relegated from the Primera División.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title1">
        The 1930s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_30">
        Although Barcelona won the very first Liga in 1929 and Real Madrid won their first titles in 1932 and 1933, it was Athletic Bilbao that set the early pace winning Primera División in 1930, 1931, 1934 and 1936. They were also runners-up in 1932 and 1933. In 1935, Real Betis, then known as Betis Balompié, won their only title to date. Primera División was suspended during the Spanish Civil War.\n
In 1937, the teams in the Republican area of Spain, with the notable exception of the two Madrid clubs, competed in the Mediterranean League and Barcelona emerged as champions. Seventy years later, on 28 September 2007, Barcelona requested the RFEF to recognise that title as a Liga title. This action was taken after RFEF was asked to recognise Levante FC\'s Copa de la España Libre win as equivalent to Copa del Rey trophy. Nevertheless, the governing body of Spanish football has not made an outright decision yet.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title2">
        The 1940s\n
        </string>

    <string name="la_liga_40">
        When the Primera División resumed after the Spanish Civil War, it was Atlético Aviación (nowadays Atlético Madrid), Valencia, and Sevilla that initially emerged as the strongest clubs. Atlético were only awarded a place during the 1939–40 season as a replacement for Real Oviedo, whose ground had been damaged during the war. The club subsequently won their first Liga title and retained it in 1941. While other clubs lost players to exile, execution, and as casualties of the war, the Atlético team was reinforced by a merger. The young, pre-war squad of Valencia had also remained intact and in the post-war years matured into champions, gaining three Liga titles in1942, 1944, and 1947. They were also runners-up in 1948 and 1949. Sevilla also enjoyed a brief golden era, finishing as runners-up in 1940 and 1942 before winning their only title to date in 1946. By the latter part of the decade, Barcelona began to emerge as a force when they were crowned champions in 1945, 1948 and 1949\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title3">
    Di Stéfano, Puskás, Kubala and Suárez\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_50">
        Naturalised Argentine Alfredo Di Stéfano was part of a dominant Real Madrid side in the 1950s\n
Although Atlético Madrid, previously known as Atlético Aviación, were champions in 1950 and 1951 under catenaccio mastermind Helenio Herrera, the 1950s saw the beginning of the Barcelona/Real Madrid dominance. During the 1930s, 1940s, and 1950s, there were strict limits imposed on foreign players. In most cases, clubs could only have three foreign players in their squads, meaning that at least eight local players had to play in every game. During the 1950s, however, these rules were circumvented by Real Madrid and Barcelona, who naturalized Alfredo Di Stéfano, Ferenc Puskás, and Ladislav Kubala. Inspired by Kubala, Barça won the title in 1952 and 1953. Di Stéfano, Puskás, and Francisco Gento formed the nucleus of the Real Madrid team that dominated the second half of the 1950s. Madrid won the first division for the first time as Real Madrid in 1954 and retained its title in 1955. They were winners again in 1957 and 1958, with only Athletic Bilbao interrupting their sequence. During this period, Real Madrid also won an unprecedented five consecutive European Cups. Barcelona, with a team coached by Helenio Herrera and featuring Luis Suárez, won the title in 1959 and 1960.\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_title4">
    The Madrid years\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_60">
Between 1961 and 1980, Real Madrid dominated the Primera División, being crowned champion 14 times. This included a five-in-a-row sequence from 1961 to 1965 and two three-in-a-row sequences (1967–1969 and 1978–1980). During this era, only Atlético Madrid offered Real Madrid any serious challenge, adding four more titles to their tally in 1966, 1970, 1973, and 1977. Of the other clubs, only Valencia in 1971 and the Johan Cruyff-inspired Barcelona of 1974 managed to break the dominance of Real Madrid.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title5">
        The Madrid winning sequence was ended more significantly in 1981 when Real Sociedad won their first-ever title. They retained it in 1982 and their two in a row was followed by another by their fellow Basques Athletic Bilbao, who won back-to-back titles in 1983 and 1984. Terry Venables led Barcelona to a solitary title in 1985 before Real Madrid won again another five in a row sequence (1986–1990) with a team guided by Leo Beenhakker and including Hugo Sánchez and the legendary La Quinta del Buitre – Emilio Butragueño, Manolo Sanchís, Martín Vázquez, Míchel and Miguel Pardeza.\n
    </string>

 <string name="la_liga_title6">
    The 1990s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_90">
        Johan Cruyff returned to Barcelona as manager in 1988, and assembled the legendary Dream Team. Cruyff introduced players like Pep Guardiola, Jose Mari Bakero,Txiki Begiristain, Andoni Goikoetxea, Ronald Koeman, Michael Laudrup, Romario and Hristo Stoichkov. This team won Primera Division four times between 1991 and 1994 and won the European Cup in 1992. Laudrup then moved to arch rivals Real Madrid, and helped them end Barcelona\'s run in 1995. Atletico Madrid won their ninth Primera Division title in 1996 before Real Madrid added another Liga trophy to their cabinet in 1997. After the success of Cruyff, another Dutchman – Ajax manager Louis van Gaal – arrived at the Camp Nou, and with the talents of Luis Figo, Luis Enrique, and Rivaldo, Barcelona again won the title in 1998 and 1999.\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_title7">
    The 2000s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_00">
As Primera División entered a new century, the Big Two of Real Madrid and Barcelona found themselves facing new challengers. Between 1993 and 2004, Deportivo La Coruña finished in the top three on ten occasions, a better record than either Real Madrid or Barcelona, and in 2000, under Javier Irureta, they became the ninth team to be crowned champions. Real Madrid won two more Liga titles in 2001 and 2003 and also the UEFA Champions League in 2000 and 2002, and won their 30th league title in 2007 after a three-year drought. They were challenged by a re-emerging Valencia in both competitions. Under the management of Héctor Cúper, Valencia finished as Champions League runners-up in 2000 and 2001. His successor, Rafael Benítez, built on this and led the club to a Liga title in 2002 and winning the double with a league title and the UEFA Cup in 2004. The 2004–05 season saw a resurgent Barcelona, inspired by the brilliant Ronaldinho, win their first title of the new century, in addition to the Liga-Champions League double in 2005–06. With world-class players like Raúl, Ruud van Nistelrooy and Gonzalo Higuaín, Real Madrid won back-to-back La Liga titles in 2006–07 and 2007–08 season. Under Pep Guardiola\'s Dream Team, powered by La Masia talents such as Lionel Messi, Xavi and Andrés Iniesta, Barcelona added three straight Liga titles (2008–09, 2009–10 and 2010–11).\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_title8">
    The 2010s\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_10">
In the 2011–12 season, Real Madrid won its 32nd title under the management of José Mourinho with a record-breaking points tally of 100, a record 121 number of goals scored, most overall (32) and away (16) wins in a single season in La Liga history. Barcelona coach Tito Vilanova matched the 100-point record a year later in 2012–13 while battling terminal cancer. Atlético Madrid won the 2013–14 title, their first in 18 years, and the first title in ten years that Real Madrid or Barcelona had not won. Barcelona won the 2014–15 season.\n
</string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_title">
        TEAM RECORDS\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team1">
        Titles\n
•	Most League Titles: 32, Real Madrid (1931–32, 1932–33, 1953–54, 1954–55, 1956–57, 1957–58, 1960–61, 1961–62, 1962–63, 1963–64, 1964–65, 1966–67, 1967–68, 1968–69, 1971–72, 1974–75, 1975–76, 1977–78, 1978–79, 1979–80, 1985–86, 1986–87, 1987–88, 1988–89, 1989–90, 1994–95, 1996–97, 2000–01, 2002–03,2006–07, 2007–08, 2011–12)\n
•	Most Consecutive League Titles: 5, Real Madrid (twice): (1960–61, 1961–62, 1962–63, 1963–64, 1964–65),(1985–86, 1986–87, 1987–88, 1988–89, 1989–90)\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_records_team2">
Top flight appearances\n
•	Most Appearances: 86, joint record (till 2015–16)\n
•	Athletic Bilbao (1929–present)\n
•	F. C. Barcelona (1929–present)\n
•	Real Madrid (1929–present)\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team3">
        Wins\n
•	Most wins overall: 1590, Real Madrid\n
•	Most wins in a season: 32, Real Madrid (2011–12), Barcelona (2012–13)\n
•	Most home wins in a season: 18, joint record:\n
•	Real Madrid (1987–88and (2009–10)\n
•	Barcelona (2009–10) and (2012–13)\n
•	Most away wins in a season: 16, Real Madrid (2011–12)\n
•	Most consecutive wins: 16, Barcelona (2010–11)\n
•	Most consecutive home wins: 39, Barcelona (16 February 1958 to 6 November 1960\n
•	Most consecutive away wins: 12, Barcelona (1 May 2010 to 12 February 2011)\n

•	100% home win record in a season:\n
•	Athletic Bilbao (9 games; 1933–34)\n
•	Athletic Bilbao (11 games; 1935–36)\n
•	Barcelona (13 games; 1948–49)\n
•	Barcelona (15 games; 1952–53)\n
•	Sevilla (15 games; 1956–57)\n
•	Barcelona (15 games; 1958–59)\n
•	Barcelona (15 games; 1959–60)\n
•	Real Madrid (15 games; 1959–60)\n
•	Real Madrid (15 games; 1962–63)\n
•	Real Madrid (17 games; 1985–86)\n
•	Longest win streaks from the start of a season: 9, Real Madrid ( 1968–69)\n

    </string>

      <string name="la_liga_records_team4">
        Draws\n
•	Most draws overall: 609, Athletic Bilbao\n
•	Most draws in a season: 17, joint record:\n
•	Espanyol (1997–98)\n
•	Racing Santander (1996–97)\n
•	Rayo Vallecano (1992–93)\n
•	Burgos (1990–91)\n
•	Mallorca (1989–90)\n
•	CD Málaga (1971–72)\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team5">
Losses\n
•	Most losses overall: 1024, Espanyol\n
•	Most losses in a season: 29, Sporting Gijón (1997–98)\n
•	Most consecutive losses in a season: 11, Las Palmas (13 December 1959 to 28 February 1960)\n
   </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team6">
    Points\n
    •	Most points overall in the top flight: 4110, Real Madrid\n
    •	Most points in a season overall: 100 (87.72% of points), Real Madrid (2011–12) and Barcelona (2012–13)\n
    •	Most points in a season home: 55, Barcelona\n
    •	Most points in a season away: 50, Real Madrid (2011–12)\n
    •	Most points in a season opening half: 55, Barcelona (2012–13)\n
    •	Most points in a season closing half: 52, Real Madrid (2009–10)\n
    </string>

    <string name="la_liga_records_team7">
Games without a loss\n
•	Most consecutive league games without a loss: 38, Real Sociedad, (29 April 1979 to 11 May 1980)\n
•	Most consecutive league games without a loss home: 121, Real Madrid (17 February 1957 to 7 March 1965)\n
•	Most consecutive league games without a loss away: 23, Barcelona (14 February 2010 to 30 April 2011)\n
    </string>

     <string name="la_liga_records_team8">
Goals\n
Team\n
•	Most league goals scored in a season: 121, Real Madrid (2011–12)\n
•	Most home league goals scored in a season: 78, Real Madrid (1989–90)\n
•	Most away league goals scored in a season: 53, Real Madrid (2014-15)\n
•	Fewest league goals scored in a season: 15, Logroñés (1994–95)\n
    </string>

        <string name="la_liga_scorers">
1	Argentina	Lionel Messi	years:2004–present	311	goals\n
2	Portugal	Cristiano Ronaldo	years:2009–present	256	goals\n
3	Spain	Telmo Zarra	years:1940–1955	251	goals\n
4	Mexico	Hugo Sánchez	years:1981–1994	234	goals\n
5	Spain	Raúl	years:1994–2010	228	goals\n
6	Argentina	Alfredo di Stéfano	years:1953–1966	227	goals\n
7	Spain	César Rodríguez	years:1939–1955	223	goals\n
8	Spain	Quini	years:1970–1987	219	goals\n
9	Spain	Pahiño	years:1943–1956	210	goals\n
10	Spain	Edmundo Suárez	years:1939–1950	195	goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_history1">
The Premier League is an English professional league for men\'s association football clubs. At the top of the English football league system, it is the country\'s primary football competition. Contested by 20 clubs, it operates on a system of promotion and relegation with the Football League. Welsh clubs that compete in the English football league system can also qualify.\n
The Premier League is a corporation in which the 20 member clubs act as shareholders. Seasons run from August to May. Teams play 38 matches each (playing each team in the league twice, home and away), totalling 380 matches in the season. Most games are played on Saturday and Sunday afternoons; others during weekday evenings. It is currently sponsored by Barclays Bank and thus officially known as the Barclays Premier League and is colloquially known as the Premiership. Outside the UK it is commonly referred to as the English Premier League (EPL).\n
The competition formed as the FA Premier League on 20 February 1992 following the decision of clubs in the Football League First Division to break away from the Football League, which was originally founded in 1888, and take advantage of a lucrative television rights deal.\n
    </string>

      <string name="english_history_title1">
       History\n
    </string>

      <string name="english_history_title2">
        Origins\n
    </string>

      <string name="english_history2">
Despite significant European success in the 1970s and early 1980s, the late 80s marked a low point for English football.
Stadiums were crumbling, supporters endured poor facilities, hooliganism was rife, and English clubs banned from European competition for five years following the Heysel Stadium disaster in 1985.
The Football League First Division, the top level of English football since 1888, was behind leagues such as Italy\'s Serie A and Spain\'s La Liga in attendances and revenues, and several top English players had moved abroad.\n
By the turn of the 1990s the downward trend was starting to reverse: at the 1990 FIFA World Cup, England reached the semi-finals;
UEFA, European football\'s governing body, lifted the five-year ban on English clubs playing in European competitions in 1990, resulting in Manchester United lifting the UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup in 1991,
          and the Taylor Report on stadium safety standards, which proposed expensive upgrades to create all-seater stadiums in the aftermath of the Hillsborough disaster, was published in January of that year.\n
Television money also become more important: the Football League received £6.3 million for a two-year agreement in 1986, but when that deal was renewed in 1988, the price rose to £44 million over four years.
The 1988 negotiations were the first signs of a breakaway league: ten clubs threatened to leave and form a "super league",
          but were eventually persuaded to stay.As stadiums improved and match attendance and revenues rose, the country\'s top teams again considered leaving the Football League in order to capitalise on the influx of money into the sport.\n

    </string>

      <string name="english_history3">
At the close of the 1991 season, a proposal was tabled for the establishment of a new league that would bring more money into the game overall. The Founder Members Agreement,
          signed on 17 July 1991 by the game\'s top-flight clubs, established the basic principles for setting up the FA Premier League. The newly formed top division would have commercial independence from The Football Association and the Football League, giving the FA Premier League licence to negotiate its own broadcast and sponsorship agreements.\n
The argument given at the time was that the extra income would allow English clubs to compete with teams across Europe.
The managing director of London Weekend Television (LWT), Greg Dyke, met with the representatives of the "big five” football clubs in England in 1990. The meeting was to pave the way for a break away from The Football League.\n
Dyke believed that it would be more lucrative for LWT if only the larger clubs in the country were featured on national television and wanted to establish whether the clubs would be interested in a larger share of television rights money. The five clubs decided it was a good idea and decided to press ahead with it; however, the league would have no credibility without the backing of The Football Association and so David Dein of Arsenal held talks to see whether the FA were receptive to the idea.\n
The FA did not enjoy an amicable relationship with the Football League at the time and considered it as a way to weaken the Football League\'s position.\n
In 1992, the First Division clubs resigned from the Football League en masse and on 27 May 1992 the FA Premier League was formed as a limited company working out of an office at the Football Association's then headquarters in Lancaster Gate.\n
This meant a break-up of the 104-year-old Football League that had operated until then with four divisions; the Premier League would operate with a single division and the Football League with three. There was no change in competition format; the same number of teams competed in the top flight, and promotion and relegation between the Premier League and the new First Division remained the same as the old First and Second Divisions with three teams relegated from the league and three promoted.\n
The league held its first season in 1992–93 and was originally composed of 22 clubs. The first ever Premier League goal was scored by Brian Deane of Sheffield United in a 2–1 win against Manchester United.The 22 inaugural members of the new Premier League were Arsenal, Aston Villa, Blackburn Rovers, Chelsea, Coventry City,Crystal Palace, Everton, Ipswich Town, Leeds United, Liverpool, Manchester City, Manchester United, Middlesbrough, Norwich City, Nottingham Forest, Oldham Athletic,Queens Park Rangers, Sheffield United, Sheffield Wednesday, Southampton, Tottenham Hotspur, and Wimbledon. Luton Town, Notts County and West Ham Unitedwere the three teams relegated from the old first division at the end of the 1991–92 season, and did not take part in the inaugural Premier League season.\n
    </string>

 <string name="english_history4">
One significant feature of the Premier League in the mid 2000s was the dominance of "Big Four" clubs Arsenal, Chelsea, Liverpool and Manchester United. During this decade, and particularly from 2002 to 2009, they dominated the top four spots,
     which came with UEFA Champions League qualification, taking all top four places in 5 out of 6 seasons from 2003–04 to 2008–09 inclusive, with Arsenal going as far as winning the league without losing a single game in 2003–04,
     the only time it has ever happened in the Premier League. In May 2008 Kevin Keegan stated that "Big Four" dominance threatened the division, "This league is in danger of becoming one of the most boring but great leagues in the world. Premier League chief executive Richard Scudamore said in defence: There are a lot of different tussles that go on in the Premier League depending on whether you\'re at the top, in the middle or at the bottom that make it interesting.\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_history5">
The years following 2009 marked a shift in the structure of the "Big Four" with Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester City both breaking into the top four. In the 2009–10 season, Tottenham finished fourth and became the first team to break the top four since Everton in 2005. Criticism of the gap between an elite group of "super clubs" and the majority of the Premier League has continued, nevertheless, due to their increasing ability to spend more than the other Premier League clubs. Manchester City won the title in the 2011–12 season, becoming the first club outside the "Big Four" to win since 1994–95. That season also saw two of the Big Four (Chelsea and Liverpool) finish outside the top four places for the first time since 1994–95\n
    </string>


     <string name="english_records_title1">
       League\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records_title2">
       Titles\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records1">
•	Most League titles: 20, Manchester United\n
•	Most consecutive League titles: 3, joint record:\n
•	Huddersfield Town (1923–24, 1924–25, 1925–26)\n
•	Arsenal (1932–33, 1933–34, 1934–35)\n
•	Liverpool (1981–82, 1982–83, 1983–84)\n
•	Manchester United (twice): (1998–99, 1999–00, 2000–01) and (2006–07, 2007–08, 2008–09)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records_title3">
       Top-flight appearances\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records2">
•	Most consecutive seasons in top flight: 90 seasons, Arsenal (1919–present, though no League football was played due to second world war between 1939 and 1945–46;)\n
•	Most seasons in top flight overall: 113 seasons, Everton\n
•	Fewest seasons in top flight overall: 1 season, joint record, Glossop, Leyton Orient, Northampton, Carlisle United, Swindon and Barnsley have completed only one season in top flight in their history.\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records_title4">
       Wins\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records3">
•	Most wins overall: 2096, Manchester United\n
•	Most wins in the top-flight overall: 1803, Liverpool\n
•	Most wins at home overall: 1341, Manchester United\n
•	Most wins at home in top-flight overall: 1174, Everton\n
•	Most wins away overall: 755, Manchester United\n
•	Most wins away in top-flight overall: 638, Arsenal\n
•	Most wins in a season: 33, Doncaster Rovers (Third Division North, 1946–47; )\n
•	Most wins in a top flight season: 31, Tottenham Hotspur (First Division, 1960–61)\n
•	Most consecutive wins: 14, joint record:\n
•	Arsenal (Premier League between 10 February 2002 and 24 August 2002) (Top-flight record)\n
•	Manchester United (Second Division, 1904–05)\n
•	Bristol City (Second Division, 1905–06)\n
•	Preston North End (Second Division, 1950–51)\n
•	Most consecutive wins without conceding a goal: 9, Stockport County (League Two between January 13, 2007 and March 3, 2007)\n
•	Most consecutive home wins: 25, Bradford Park Avenue (Third Division North, 1926–27)\n
•	Most consecutive home wins top flight: 21, Liverpool (1972)\n
•	Most consecutive away wins in top flight: 12 Arsenal (Premier League between March 3, 2013 and October 26, 2013)\n
•	Fewest wins in a season: 1, joint record:\n
•	Derby County (Premier League, 2007–08))\n
•	Loughborough (Second Division, 1899–1900))\n
•	100%home win record in a season:\n
•	Sunderland (13 games; First Division, 1891–92)\n
•	Liverpool (14 games; Second Division, 1893–94)\n
•	Bury (15 games; Second Division, 1894–95)\n
•	Sheffield Wednesday (17 games; Second Division, 1899–1900)\n
•	Small Heath (17 games; Second Division, 1902–03)\n
•	Brentford (21 games; Third Division South, 1929–30)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_history_title5">
       Draws\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records4">
•	Most draws overall in the top flight: 1069, Everton\n
•	Most draws in a season: 23, joint record\n
•	Norwich City (from 42 games, First Division, 1978–79)\n
•	Exeter City (from 46 games, Fourth Division, 1986–87)\n
•	Hartlepool United (from 46 games, Third Division, 1997–98)\n
•	Cardiff City (from 46 games, Third Division, 1997–98)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_history_title6">
       Losses\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records5">
•	Most losses overall in the top flight: 1470, Everton\n
•	Most losses in a season: 34, Doncaster Rovers, (Third Division, 1997–98; )\n
•	Fewest losses: 0, joint record:\n
•	Preston North End (First Division, 1888–89; final record P22 W18 D4 L0)\n
•	Arsenal (Premier League, 2003–04; final record P38 W26 D12 L0)\n
•	Liverpool (Second Division, 1893-94; final record P28 W22 D6 L0)\n
•	Most consecutive losses\n
•	18, Darwen, 1898–1899 (Second Division)\n
•	17, Rochdale, 1931–32 (Division 3 North)\n
•	17, Sunderland, 2002-2003 (15 in top tier)\n

    </string>

     <string name="english_history_title7">
       Points\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records6">
•	Most points overall in the top flight: Liverpool\n
•	Most points in a season (2 points for a win): 74, Lincoln City (Fourth Division, 1975–76)\n
•	Most points in a season (3 points for a win): 106, Reading (Championship, 2005–06)\n
•	Most points in a season for a top-flight team (2 points for a win, 42 games): 68 (30 wins 8 draws), Liverpool (First Division, 1978–79)\n
•	Most points in a season for a top-flight team (3 points for a win, 38 games): 95 (29 wins 8 draws), Chelsea (Premier League, 2004–05)\n
•	Fewest points in a season (2 points for a win): 8, joint record:\n
•	Loughborough (Second Division, 1899–1900)\n
•	Doncaster Rovers (Second Division, 1904–05)\n
•	Fewest points in a season (3 points for a win): 11, Derby County (Premier League, 2007–08)\n
•	Most points in a season while being relegated (3 points for a win): 54, joint record:\n
•	Southend United (Third Division, 21st of 24; 1988–89)\n
•	Peterborough United (Championship, 22nd of 24; 2012-13\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_history_title8">
       Goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_records7">
•	Most league goals scored in a season: (134) Peterborough United (Fourth Division, 1960–61)\n
•	Most top-flight goals scored in a season (42 games): 128, Aston Villa (First Division, 1930–31)\n
•	Most top flight goals scored in total: 6699, Everton.\n
•	Most home league goals scored in a season: 87, Millwall (Third Division South, 1927–28)\n
•	Most away league goals scored in a season: 60, Arsenal (First Division, 1930–31)\n
•	Most consecutive games scoring: 55, Arsenal (Premier League 19 May 2001 – 30 November 2002)\n
•	Most consecutive games without scoring: 11, Coventry\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_records8">
•	Most titles won by an individual player: 13, Ryan Giggs\n
•	Most career league appearances: 1,005 (849 in First Division), Peter Shilton (1966 to 1997)\n
•	Most career league appearances by an outfield player: 931, Tony Ford (1975 to 2002)\n
•	Most career league appearances at one club: 770, John Trollope (Swindon Town, 1960 to 1980)\n
•	Most career top flight league appearances at one club: 672, Ryan Giggs (Manchester United, 1991 to 6 May 2014)\n
•	Most career consecutive league appearances: 375, Harold Bell (Tranmere Rovers), 1946 to 1955 (401 consecutive club games including 26 FA Cup appearances)\n
•	Oldest player: Neil McBain, 51 years and 20 days (for New Brighton v. Hartlepool United, 1947)\n
•	Youngest player: Reuben Noble-Lazarus, 15 years and 45 days (for Barnsley v. Ipswich Town, 30 September 2008)\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_history_title9">
       Goals\n
    </string>

    <string name="english_records9">
•	Most career league goals: 434, Arthur Rowley (619 matches, for West Bromwich Albion, Fulham, Leicester City and Shrewsbury Town, 1946 to 1965)\n
•	Most career top-flight goals: 357, Jimmy Greaves (516 matches, for Chelsea, Tottenham Hotspur and West Ham United, 1957 to 1971)\n
•	Most consecutive top flight league matches scored in: 12, Jimmy Dunne, for Sheffield United between 24-October-1931 and 1-January-1932, 18 goals in all.\n
•	Most goals in a season: 60, Dixie Dean (39 matches, for Everton 1927–28)\n
•	Most goals in a game: 10, Joe Payne (for Luton Town v. Bristol Rovers, 13 April 1936)\n
•	Most goals in a top flight game: 7, Ted Drake for Arsenal v. Aston Villa (away), 14 December 1935\n
•	Fastest goal: 3.5 seconds, Colin Cowperthwaite (for Barrow v. Kettering Town, 1979)\n
•	Fastest goal on a League debut: 7 seconds, Freddy Eastwood (for Southend United v. Swansea City, 16 October 2004)\n
•	Fastest hat-trick (time between first and third goals): 2 minutes 20 seconds, James Hayter (for AFC Bournemouth v. Wrexham, 23 February 2004)\n
•	Fastest goal by a substitute: 1.8 seconds, Nicklas Bendtner (for Arsenal v. Tottenham Hotspur, 22 December 2007)\n
•	Most own goals in one season: 5, Bobby Stuart (Middlesbrough, 1934–35)\n
    </string>

     <string name="english_records10">
1	  Alan Shearer Blackburn Rovers, Newcastle United 260 goals\n
2	  Wayne Rooney Everton, Manchester United 192 goals\n
3	  Andy Cole Newcastle United, Manchester United, Blackburn Rovers, Fulham, Manchester City,Portsmouth 187 goals\n
4	  Frank Lampard West Ham United, Chelsea, Manchester City 177 goals\n
5	  Thierry Henry Arsenal 175 goals\n
6	  Robbie Fowler Liverpool, Leeds United, Manchester City 163 goals\n
7	  Michael Owen Liverpool, Newcastle United, Manchester United, Stoke City 150 goals\n
8	  Les Ferdinand Queens Park Rangers, Newcastle United, Tottenham Hotspur, West Ham United,Leicester City, Bolton Wanderers 149 goals\n
9	  Teddy Sheringham Nottingham Forest, Tottenham Hotspur, Manchester United, Portsmouth, West Ham United 146 goals\n
10	  Robin van Persie Arsenal, Manchester United 144 goals\n
    </string>

</resources>
